<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<CNJExport>
	<Item>
		<ID>52284948316497</ID>
		<name>HYDROMAX 7 TRANSPARENT PENIS INCREASE PUMP</name>
		<description>Do you want to maximize your potential? Bathmate is the ultimate brand in penis pumps, using water pressure to generate long-lasting gains in length and girth. It is patented under the name Hydro, one of the best-selling penis enlargement devices in the world. Bathmate pumps are designed to be used in the bath or shower, offering a convenient and effective way to exercise your manhood, resulting in natural growth. The collection offers a wide variety of pumps, from classic models in various sizes to the Hydro X series, pumps with higher intensity and faster results. In addition to innovative hydraulic pressure pumps, Bathmate also sells a large selection of powerful cock rings, perfect for increasing durability and potency. The Hydromax7 pump is the perfect choice for men who want to lengthen their penis and increase stamina. This pump keeps the penis in tip-top shape, increasing blood pressure for a more impressive erection. The Hydromax7 pump is larger than the Hydro and has a soft seal and a very comfortable ring. This pump is designed for total comfort and the textured detail of the empty tube allows for easier control thanks to a great grip. This pump dilates blood vessels and the shut-off valve allows for one-handed filling for greater convenience. Transparent color</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/bathmate-hydromax-7-transparent-penis-increase-pump?variant=52284948316497</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/hydromax-7-transparent-penis-increase-pump-5916409.jpg?v=1775073081</mainImage>
		<price>110.90</price>
		<brand>BATHMATE</brand>
		<productCode>D-218220</productCode>
		<quantity>50</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>5060140209560</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>52284948349265</ID>
		<name>HYDROMAX 9 TRANSPARENT PENIS INCREASE PUMP</name>
		<description>A revolutionary concept for penis development. The HydroMax 9 pump is the latest in hydrotechnology for penis enlargement, development and health. Finally there is finally a new truth bomb. With more than 50 new features compared to the standard Bathmate model, the HydroMax 9 model has 35% more power and a super comfortable sleeve for maximum comfort during use. The HydroMax extends up to 15% more than the HydroMax 7 and can also be rotated 360º for maximum comfort and power. It is designed for penises from 17.8 cm to 23 cm when erect. Its system incorporates a new, much softer and more comfortable sealing system at the base of the penis and testicles that reduces the sensation of pressure but not performance. Its rotating system allows you to rotate 360º so that you have a complete view at the angle you prefer when you are using it during the bath or shower. It also incorporates a scale so you can see your improvement. The internal gusset size has been increased and the number of convolutions reduced to allow you to gain even more thickness. There is none like Bathmate's Hydromax 9. It is powerful, resistant and super comfortable to use: Its benefits: Increases penis length Increases the thickness of the penis Gain volume quickly Increase your self-esteem Reduces penile tilt Widens the glans Helps last longer in relationships.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/bathmate-hydromax-9-transparent-penis-increase-pump?variant=52284948349265</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/hydromax-9-transparent-penis-increase-pump-9465643.jpg?v=1775073010</mainImage>
		<price>132.90</price>
		<brand>BATHMATE</brand>
		<productCode>D-218222</productCode>
		<quantity>12</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>5060140209362</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>52284989440337</ID>
		<name>CLOUD DANCER BLUE AIR PULSE VIBRATOR</name>
		<description>You are romantic? Do you need candlelight and soft music? Then the Satisfyer Cloud Dancer is the perfect pleasure toy for you! This adorable pressure wave vibrator featuring Satisfyer's innovative Air Pulse technology has a unique and dreamy look: the transparent outer layer made of soft silicone, the haptically appealing curves and the charming cloud design are simply beautiful to fall in love with. . This makes it not only the perfect choice for all the hopeless romantics, but also the ideal gift to introduce someone to the Satisfyer range of Double Air Pulse vibrators.The Cloud Dancer is beautifully designed because, as we all know, presentation matters. But what will satisfy you are the internal advantages of the vibrator: 11 pressure wave intensities and 12 vibration programs can be combined as you like. Contactless clitoral stimulation combined with exciting vibrations is a pleasure not only for solo play. Thanks to its compact size and charming design, the Cloud Dancer is also absolutely suitable for intimate moments as a couple, even in the bathtub or shower thanks to its waterproof finish (IPX7). The adorable Air Pulse vibrator is made of skin-friendly, hygienic silicone and can be easily cleaned with toy cleaner or warm water and mild soap. The included USB charging cable gives your romantic friend full power again and again. Let yourself be seduced and enjoy pleasurable and sensual moments with the adorable Satisfyer Cloud Dancer! Characteristics: 15 year warranty Stimulation of the clitoris using pressure and vibration waves. Body-friendly silicone Water resistant (IPX7) 11 pressure wave intensities + 12 vibration settings 2 independently controlled motors whisper mode Easy to clean Rechargeable lithium ion battery. Magnetic USB charging cable included</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/satisfyer-cloud-dancer-blue-air-pulse-vibrator?variant=52284989440337</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/cloud-dancer-blue-air-pulse-vibrator-4174610.jpg?v=1775073076</mainImage>
		<price>59.95</price>
		<brand>SATISFYER</brand>
		<productCode>D-237591</productCode>
		<quantity>45</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4061504049700</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53232772907345</ID>
		<name>TITAN AND CLIONA COUPLES SET</name>
		<description>Are you ready for some good vibes? Immerse yourself in the deepest parts of your pleasure with this Titan and Cliona couples set. TITAN by KIIROO™ is a masturbator with touch-sensitive vibration technology. And Cliona is a powerful, waterproof pocket clitoral massager, perfect for anyone on the go or at home. Using the touch-sensitive features, these two products can lead to something wild Can: Control the vibration intensity with a simple touch. Transmit touch to your partner's device from a distance. Have your pleasure controlled by your partner. Let your pleasure be controlled by compatible online content. What you get: Cliona by KIIROO™ Cliona™ by KIIROO® USB charging cable Authenticity and warranty card Quick Setup Manual TITAN by Kiiroo™ Interactive Stroker Vibrator TITAN by Kiiroo™ Interactive Stroker Vibrator USB charging cable Authenticity and warranty card Quick Setup Manual</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-titan-and-cliona-lilac-couples-set?variant=53232772907345</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/titan-and-cliona-couples-set-5852862.jpg?v=1775073036</mainImage>
		<price>194.21</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-228358</productCode>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8719324994699</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53232786538833</ID>
		<name>PRO 2 KISS WAVE CLITORIS STIMULATOR</name>
		<description>Travel size, mini air wave clitoral massager, discreet, looks like a mascara or lipstick, fits perfectly in your purse or bag. USB rechargeable via your iPhone USB-C cable. Easy to use and quiet, 3 speeds of 10 different air pressure wave modes. 3 x 10 pressure wave programs 3D air pulse peak control Body-friendly silicone Travel size Quiet Rechargeable (USB-C), cable NOT included This discreet and slim device fits perfectly in your purse or bag. The Satisfyer 4D Magnetic Power Motor is a powerful, easy-to-use device that fits in the palm of your hand and is perfect for travel. With the new patented 4D Magnetic Power Motor, Satisfyer takes contactless clitoral stimulation to the next level. This cutting-edge technology redefines the sensory experience, delivering quiet yet powerful stimulation with gentle pressure waves. The inner membrane of this device can be moved at the push of a button - the closer the membrane is to the opening, the stronger the pressure waves. Three LED lights on the front indicate the position of the membrane so the user easily knows what intensity it is on. – 3 LEDs on - the membrane is closer to the opening, providing intense and powerful sensations.– 2 LEDs on: the membrane is in the middle, offering a balanced wave force.– 1 LED on: the membrane is further away, perfect for a softer touch. With 11 pressure wave programs and 3 membrane positions, you have 33 incredible ways to explore your desires. Main Features 33 Programs: 11 Pressure Wave Programs and 3 Membrane Positions With the innovative 4D Magnetic Power Motor USB Type-C charging port (cable NOT included) LED button to indicate the membrane position Stylish lipstick design with hygienic cap Made of skin-friendly silicone body Waterproof (IPX7) 15-year warranty</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/satisfyer-pro-2-kiss-wave-clitoris-stimulator-garnet-black?variant=53232786538833</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/pro-2-kiss-wave-clitoris-stimulator-black-5604916.jpg?v=1775073075</mainImage>
		<price>41.31</price>
		<brand>SATISFYER</brand>
		<productCode>D-242637</productCode>
		<quantity>31</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4061504078601</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53232788767057</ID>
		<name>ONYX+ TELEDILDONIC MASTURBATOR</name>
		<description>KIIROO Onyx+ brings a whole new sensory experience to the internet: intimate touch. This lightweight male masturbator is quiet, discreet and perfect as a travel companion. The third generation Onyx has a completely different rotary motor that changes the feel of what it feels. Onyx+ can reach up to 140 beats per minute while maintaining a quieter motor than its two predecessors, making the sensory experience of using Onyx+ even more exciting. Inside Onyx+ are 10 rings that work together to simulate vaginal or anal intercourse and stroke up and down in real time. Connect your KIIROO Onyx+ with any KIIROO device. KIIROO Pearl (1 or 2), KIIROO Onyx (1, 2 or +), OhMiBod Fuse, OhMiBod Esca (1 or 2), or any FeelTechnology compatible device. You can send and receive data from those devices. In short, you can truly feel your partner's touch, in real time, from anywhere in the world. If you prefer solo sessions, KIIROO Onyx+ can be combined with your favorite interactive content; associated sites for erotic videos, virtual reality, 3D games and webcams. All content from FeelMe.com and other interactive partner sites are supported. Product specifications: · Materials: ABS, SILICONE · Sleeve: SuperSkin sleeve · Finish: smooth and shiny touch · Size: 8.9X7.9X26.3cm · Opening hole size: 5X4.5cm · Hole height: 16.5cm · Weight: 1.3kgs with box · Battery: 1000 mAh lithium ion polymer · Charging: 4 hours · Use time: 1 hour What you get in the box: - KIIROO Onyx + - USB charging cable - Authenticity and warranty card - Quick Setup Manual - RealFeel Sleeve</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-onyx-teledildonic-masturbator-with-skin-texture?variant=53232788767057</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/onyx-teledildonic-masturbator-7139826.png?v=1775073045</mainImage>
		<price>131.40</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-227152</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8719324994354</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53232800661841</ID>
		<name>TITAN TECHNOLOGICAL MASTURBATOR</name>
		<description>Titan by Kiiro is an interactive male masturbator with the innovative touch-sensitive vibration system that incorporates 9 vibrating bullets that will intensify the sensations in male masturbation. DESIGNED TO PROLONG RESISTANCE AND INCREASE MALE PLEASURE. Titan can connect to more than 4,000 interactive videos from different content platforms. Being able to feel the movements made by your favorite actresses, whether 2D or in virtual reality. Titan can also connect to other Kiiro devices from anywhere in the world, sharing the pleasure with other users using the touch-sensitive controls, controlling the speed and intensity of vibrations on the devices of other connected users. It incorporates 6 vibration modes. Charging time is 3 hours to 3.5 hours, for a use time of 30 to 40 minutes. INTERACTIVE SESSIONS ARE THE FUTURE!!!You can enjoy sessions with other users who also have an interactive toy (there are a lot of them). You have the possibility to control your pleasure and vice versa. Simply download the FeelConnect mobile app, connect the interactive toy to the app and scan the QR code at any webcam site. HOW TO CONNECT WITH THE FEEL CONNECT APP: 1.Download the Feel Connect application on your phone and click on “Add a Device” in the menu at the top left. 2. Turn on the interactive toy and activate Bluetooth mode on the phone. 3. Wait for the application to find the device, then click “add select devices” at the bottom of the screen. 4. The device is now connected to the feel connect app and is ready to use. 5. Now the website you like the most will be added. Click on “add website” in the upper right menu. The app will open a QR code. 6. Now you have to leave your mobile for a moment and go to your computer to search for one of the compatible websites. Start recording and click on the button that says “interactive button”. Keep in mind that each site has its own connection experience. 7.Scan the code that appears when you click on the “interactive button” and you will be ready to start. From now on, the interactive toy will vibrate every time another user sends a tip. 8. Now you are ready to start a new interactive session. This process should only be done once. Every time you want to be interactive again, just turn on the toy and open the app on your phone.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-titan-technological-masturbator?variant=53232800661841</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/titan-technological-masturbator-5645963.jpg?v=1775073103</mainImage>
		<price>123.13</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-227157</productCode>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8719324994071</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53232800694609</ID>
		<name>TITAN EXPERIENCE TECHNOLOGICAL MASTURBATOR</name>
		<description>Titan by Kiiro is an interactive male masturbator with the innovative touch-sensitive vibration system that incorporates 9 vibrating bullets that will intensify the sensations in male masturbation. DESIGNED TO PROLONG RESISTANCE AND INCREASE MALE PLEASURE. Titan can connect to more than 4,000 interactive videos from different content platforms. Being able to feel the movements made by your favorite actresses, whether 2D or in virtual reality. Titan can also connect to other Kiiro devices from anywhere in the world, sharing the pleasure with other users using the touch-sensitive controls, controlling the speed and intensity of vibrations on the devices of other connected users. It incorporates 6 vibration modes. Charging time is 3 hours to 3.5 hours, for a use time of 30 to 40 minutes. INTERACTIVE SESSIONS ARE THE FUTURE!!!You can enjoy sessions with other users who also have an interactive toy (there are a lot of them). You have the possibility to control your pleasure and vice versa. Simply download the FeelConnect mobile app, connect the interactive toy to the app and scan the QR code at any webcam site. HOW TO CONNECT WITH THE FEEL CONNECT APP: 1.Download the Feel Connect application on your phone and click on “Add a Device” in the menu at the top left. 2. Turn on the interactive toy and activate Bluetooth mode on the phone. 3. Wait for the application to find the device, then click “add select devices” at the bottom of the screen. 4. The device is now connected to the feel connect app and is ready to use. 5. Now the website you like the most will be added. Click on “add website” in the upper right menu. The app will open a QR code. 6. Now you have to leave your mobile for a moment and go to your computer to search for one of the compatible websites. Start recording and click on the button that says “interactive button”. Keep in mind that each site has its own connection experience. 7.Scan the code that appears when you click on the “interactive button” and you will be ready to start. From now on, the interactive toy will vibrate every time another user sends a tip. 8. Now you are ready to start a new interactive session. This process should only be done once. Every time you want to be interactive again, just turn on the toy and open the app on your phone. Titan Experience comes with a special design signed by Asa Akira, Bobbi Eden, Jessica Drake, Lisa Ann, ROMI - Rain and Tanya Tate USB charging cable, Instruction manual, Authenticity card, Access to Kiiroo's exclusive adult platform and 1500 free Tokens (digital currency unit) to spend on its interactive video website. Titan Experience will imitate the actions of Asa Akira, Bobbi Eden, Jessica Drake, Lisa Ann, ROMI - Rain and Tanya Tate as seen in the interactive videos.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-titan-experience-technological-masturbator?variant=53232800694609</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/titan-experience-technological-masturbator-8741769.jpg?v=1775073147</mainImage>
		<price>127.26</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-227158</productCode>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8719324994088</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53232801382737</ID>
		<name>KEON WIFI COMBO AUTOMATIC MASTURBATOR + FEEL STROKER</name>
		<description>Keon WiFi with FeelStroker: Interactive, Fully Synchronized PleasureDiscover next-level stimulation with Keon WiFi and the original Kiiroo FeelStroker: a powerful combination designed to sync in real-time with virtual reality, adult videos, and webcam interactions. Keon WiFis ergonomic design and advanced connectivity deliver powerful, automatic movements that stay in perfect rhythm with your favorite content. The FeelStroker amplifies every movement with a soft silicone tunnel and large stimulating nubs, created to intensify sensation and immerse you in pleasure. Uninterrupted Pleasure - Designed for smooth, responsive pleasure, Keon WiFi syncs in real-time with your favorite content, cam shows, and connected partners. Sync your movements with 2D content on over 200 adult sites on FeelMe AI www.FeelMe.com, connect directly to interactive webcams, or link up with your partner via the FeelConnect app for immersive intimacy, no matter the distance. Its not your ordinary masturbator - This realistic masturbator features a smooth, body-safe silicone tunnel with large stimulating nubs and detailed entry for ultimate realism. Use it with Keon WiFi to sync every movement with your favorite adult scenes for deep, immersive satisfaction. Wi-Fi and Bluetooth enabled - Keon WiFi provides connectivity Wi-Fi and Bluetooth for more reliable synchronization and smoother performance in interactive videos, games, and live content. With real-time response, it provides uninterrupted, immersive pleasure thats more synchronized than ever. FEATURES: Controllable stroke length with up to 230 strokes per minute. Compatible with various Keon accessories. Compatible with over 30 types of masturbators strokers. Connect with your partner using FeelConnect. Connect to adult content with AI FeelMe. Ergonomic shape and intuitive grip control. Customizable settings and plugins. Connection to partner devices. Wi-Fi and Bluetooth activated for seamless syncing. SPECIFICATIONS: Keon: Materials: ABS, PC, Silicone Finish: Matte and glossy Weight: 1.16 kg Height: 230 mm Width: 130mm Length: 146 mm Battery: Lithium-ion 700 mAh Water resistant: No Feel Stroker: Materials: ABS, PC, TPE Weight: 585 g Height: 235 mm Width: 88mm Length: 88 mm Water resistant: Yes Box contents: 1 x Keon by Kiiroo 1 x Feel Stroker generic pale color 1 x USB Charging Cable 1 x Code Card</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-keon-wifi-combo-automatic-masturbator-feel-stroker?variant=53232801382737</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/keon-wifi-combo-automatic-masturbator-feel-stroker-5258368.jpg?v=1775073083</mainImage>
		<price>205.78</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-244530</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8720938956348</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53594109772113</ID>
		<name>DUO NEXT CLITORAL STIMULATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>Dual clitoral and G-spot stimulator with 3D Pleasure Air. An advanced dual stimulator that combines Womanizer’s revolutionary 3D Pleasure Air with We-Vibe’s deep, rumbly G-spot vibrations. This powerful combination is designed to create next-level blended orgasms that feel more natural, intense, and personal than ever before. Next Duo is the latest in dual stimulation: it combines advanced 3D Pleasure Air technology for the clitoris with deep, rumbly vibrations for the G-spot. Designed to deliver more intense sensations and blended orgasms, it’s your gateway to mind-blowing pleasure. 14 vibration intensity levels – Start slowly and build up to an epic climax with deep, rumbly vibrations that transition smoothly between intensity levels. 10 vibration patterns – Find your rhythm and try something new, whether you prefer a steady pulse, a low-to-high crescendo, or an exciting wave. Separate motor controls – Control Pleasure Air and vibrations together or independently for maximum customization. 3D Pleasure Air – 3D Pleasure Air uses pulsating air pressure to mimic natural suction and deliver a deeper, more realistic sensation. 14 intensity levels – Whether you prefer gentle and delicate pleasure, powerful and intense sensations, or something in between, your next orgasm is just a button press away. Perfectly balanced intensity levels offer the ideal setting for every mood. IPX7 waterproof – Ready to dive deeper? Because your Womanizer is IPX7 waterproof, nothing will stop you from enjoying a long, relaxing bath, a refreshing shower, or even poolside fun. Climax Control – The new Climax Control feature creates a deeper, richer sensation, taking our original Pleasure Air stimulation into a new 3D dimension. You can now control not only the speed and intensity of your massage, but also the depth of the air waves. The three Climax Control levels offer a more nuanced, fuller multiple-orgasm experience. Body-safe silicone – The surface is made from soft-touch silicone for a silky feel on the skin. This body-safe material is free from phthalates, BPA, and latex—a true delight for the skin. Whisper-quiet – Our quietest model to date, operating virtually silently without sacrificing power. Designed for discretion, Next removes distractions and focuses on pure pleasure. Twilight Glow – With a brief press of the power button, your toy quickly returns to its lowest setting for a relaxing orgasmic finish. USB charging port – Magnetic pins make recharging fast and convenient. Smart Silence – Innovative Smart Silence technology lets you indulge your desires. The toy only activates when it touches your skin; when not in use, it goes into standby mode. This makes it quieter and allows you to enjoy the moment without distractions. FEATURES: Dark purple, dark pink, black IPX7 waterproof Runtime: 120 minutes Charging time: 120 minutes Materials: Body-safe silicone Weight: 274 grams Dimensions: 56 x 81 x 195 mm Packaging dimensions: 146 x 66 x 211 mm Box includes: Womanizer Next Cotton storage pouch Additional stimulation head (size M) Quick start guide Compliance and safety information #Memasturbo sticker USB cable</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-duo-next-dual-clitoral-g-spot-stimulator-black?variant=53594109772113</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/duo-next-clitoral-stimulator-dark-purple-4383779.png?v=1775073027</mainImage>
		<price>180.98</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-245098</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460632287</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53602827731281</ID>
		<name>DUO 2 STIMULATOR-Black</name>
		<description>Indulge in whole body orgasms with the Womanizer Duo 2! The DUO2 is a unique premium rabbit toy that combines sensational clitoral stimulation with powerful G-Spot massages to create advanced, toe-curling orgasms. The Pleasure Air technology stimulates the clitoris with the perfect balance of pulsating and massaging changes in air pressure without touching the clitoris. This ensures that your most sensitive area is never over-stimulated while you experience multiple levels of intensity, giving you next level orgasms. This incredible clitoral sensation is combined with deep G-Spot stimulation via the vibrating shaft. With a bulbous head on a flexible neck, the 10 vibration patterns are delivered right where you need them with ease. The vibrations and air pulsations are controlled separately and easily via soft-touch buttons on the top of the stimulator head. With the Smart Silent mode, the DUO 2 will only turn on when in direct contact with your skin, keeping the already quiet rumbles even quieter. With the Afterglow feature, press the power button briefly after climax, bringing the intensity of the DUO 2 down to level 3 for a relaxing finish. Made with boy-safe silicone, the DUO 2 is waterproof so you can extend playtime into the bath or shower! Always use a water-based lubricant with the DUO 2 and remember to clean it with a toy cleaner before and after every use. Take your orgasms to the next level with the Womanizer DUO 2 dual stimulator! Key Features: Dual Stimulator G-Spot and Clitoral Stimulation Pleasure Air Technology 14 Intensity Levels 10 Vibration Patterns Ergonomic Flexible Shape Separate Controls Waterproof IPX7 Additional Stimulation Head Body-Safe Silicone Soft and Smooth Touch Smart Silence Feature Afterglow Setting BPA, Phthalate, Latex Free Magnetic USB Rechargeable Charge Time: 120 Mins Up to 120 Mins of Playtime Box Contents: Womanizer DUO 2 Dual Stimulator USB Charging Cable Two Stimulation Heads Cotton Storage Pouch Quick-Start Guide Safety Instructions</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-duo-2-stimulator-black?variant=53602827731281</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/duo-2-stimulator-black-6657605.png?v=1775073023</mainImage>
		<price>172.72</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235683</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460611107</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53602827764049</ID>
		<name>DUO 2 STIMULATOR-Lilac</name>
		<description>Indulge in whole body orgasms with the Womanizer Duo 2! The DUO2 is a unique premium rabbit toy that combines sensational clitoral stimulation with powerful G-Spot massages to create advanced, toe-curling orgasms. The Pleasure Air technology stimulates the clitoris with the perfect balance of pulsating and massaging changes in air pressure without touching the clitoris. This ensures that your most sensitive area is never over-stimulated while you experience multiple levels of intensity, giving you next level orgasms. This incredible clitoral sensation is combined with deep G-Spot stimulation via the vibrating shaft. With a bulbous head on a flexible neck, the 10 vibration patterns are delivered right where you need them with ease. The vibrations and air pulsations are controlled separately and easily via soft-touch buttons on the top of the stimulator head. With the Smart Silent mode, the DUO 2 will only turn on when in direct contact with your skin, keeping the already quiet rumbles even quieter. With the Afterglow feature, press the power button briefly after climax, bringing the intensity of the DUO 2 down to level 3 for a relaxing finish. Made with boy-safe silicone, the DUO 2 is waterproof so you can extend playtime into the bath or shower! Always use a water-based lubricant with the DUO 2 and remember to clean it with a toy cleaner before and after every use. Take your orgasms to the next level with the Womanizer DUO 2 dual stimulator! Key Features: Dual Stimulator G-Spot and Clitoral Stimulation Pleasure Air Technology 14 Intensity Levels 10 Vibration Patterns Ergonomic Flexible Shape Separate Controls Waterproof IPX7 Additional Stimulation Head Body-Safe Silicone Soft and Smooth Touch Smart Silence Feature Afterglow Setting BPA, Phthalate, Latex Free Magnetic USB Rechargeable Charge Time: 120 Mins Up to 120 Mins of Playtime Box Contents: Womanizer DUO 2 Dual Stimulator USB Charging Cable Two Stimulation Heads Cotton Storage Pouch Quick-Start Guide Safety Instructions</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-duo-2-stimulator-black?variant=53602827764049</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/duo-2-stimulator-lilac-5116078.png?v=1775073086</mainImage>
		<price>172.72</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235687</productCode>
		<quantity>25</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460611145</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53602827796817</ID>
		<name>DUO 2 STIMULATOR-Blue</name>
		<description>Indulge in whole body orgasms with the Womanizer Duo 2! The DUO2 is a unique premium rabbit toy that combines sensational clitoral stimulation with powerful G-Spot massages to create advanced, toe-curling orgasms. The Pleasure Air technology stimulates the clitoris with the perfect balance of pulsating and massaging changes in air pressure without touching the clitoris. This ensures that your most sensitive area is never over-stimulated while you experience multiple levels of intensity, giving you next level orgasms. This incredible clitoral sensation is combined with deep G-Spot stimulation via the vibrating shaft. With a bulbous head on a flexible neck, the 10 vibration patterns are delivered right where you need them with ease. The vibrations and air pulsations are controlled separately and easily via soft-touch buttons on the top of the stimulator head. With the Smart Silent mode, the DUO 2 will only turn on when in direct contact with your skin, keeping the already quiet rumbles even quieter. With the Afterglow feature, press the power button briefly after climax, bringing the intensity of the DUO 2 down to level 3 for a relaxing finish. Made with boy-safe silicone, the DUO 2 is waterproof so you can extend playtime into the bath or shower! Always use a water-based lubricant with the DUO 2 and remember to clean it with a toy cleaner before and after every use. Take your orgasms to the next level with the Womanizer DUO 2 dual stimulator! Key Features: Dual Stimulator G-Spot and Clitoral Stimulation Pleasure Air Technology 14 Intensity Levels 10 Vibration Patterns Ergonomic Flexible Shape Separate Controls Waterproof IPX7 Additional Stimulation Head Body-Safe Silicone Soft and Smooth Touch Smart Silence Feature Afterglow Setting BPA, Phthalate, Latex Free Magnetic USB Rechargeable Charge Time: 120 Mins Up to 120 Mins of Playtime Box Contents: Womanizer DUO 2 Dual Stimulator USB Charging Cable Two Stimulation Heads Cotton Storage Pouch Quick-Start Guide Safety Instructions</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-duo-2-stimulator-black?variant=53602827796817</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/duo-2-stimulator-blue-9785313.png?v=1775073024</mainImage>
		<price>172.72</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235685</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460611121</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603059532113</ID>
		<name>ENHANCE CLITORIAL STIMULATOR-Lilac</name>
		<description>2-in-1 clitoral stimulator with Pleasure Air and vibrations. Womanizer’s Pleasure Air technology combined with the deep, rumbly vibrations of We-Vibe for enhanced clitoral stimulation. The first Womanizer clitoral stimulator combines We-Vibe vibrations with Pleasure Air technology for heightened sensation. Independent motors allow you to use these types of stimulation together or separately, offering greater variety in your orgasmic experience. 2-in-1 Pleasure Air and Vibration Technology – Womanizer’s original Pleasure Air technology combined with We-Vibe’s powerful vibrations for enhanced stimulation. Separate Controls – Control the vibration motor and the Pleasure Air motor independently or together to enjoy more than 1,000 ways to play. Wide Stimulation Head – Intensifies orgasms by creating contact with more erogenous zones, targeting a wider area for an enhanced orgasmic experience. 10 Intensity Levels – Whether you prefer gentle and delicate pleasure, powerful and intense sensations, or something in between, your next orgasm is just a button press away. Perfectly balanced intensity levels provide the ideal setting for every mood. 10 Vibration Intensity Levels – Start slowly and build up to an epic climax with deep, rumbly vibrations that transition smoothly between intensity levels. 10 Vibration Patterns – Find your rhythm and try something new, whether you prefer a steady pulse, a low-to-high crescendo, or an exciting wave. Body-Safe Silicone – The surface is made of soft-touch silicone for a silky feel on the skin. This body-safe material is free from phthalates, BPA, and latex—a true delight for the skin. IPX7 Waterproof – Ready to dive deeper? As your Womanizer is IPX7 waterproof, nothing will stop you from enjoying a long, relaxing bath, a refreshing shower, or even poolside fun. Magnetic Charging – Magnetic pins make recharging fast and convenient. FEATURES: Vibrant pink, black, lilac IPX7 waterproof Runtime: 120 minutes Charging time: 120 minutes Materials: ABS plastic, body-safe silicone Weight: 148 grams Dimensions: Length: 158 x Height: 50 x Width: 52 mm Packaging dimensions: 184.5 x 107.75 x 67.5 mm Box includes: Womanizer Enhance Cotton storage pouch Quick start guide Compliance and safety information #Memasturbo sticker USB cable with magnetic charging pins (AC adapter not included)</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-enhance-clitorial-stimulator-lilac?variant=53603059532113</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/enhance-clitorial-stimulator-lilac-3082686.png?v=1775073044</mainImage>
		<price>131.40</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-245096</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460630665</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603350643025</ID>
		<name>VIBE LAY-ON SILENT VIBRATOR-Dark blue</name>
		<description>Silent vibrator by Womanizer. A quiet vibrator that delivers a new sensation with UltraWave Vibration, combining deep, low-frequency rumbles with 10 powerful harmonic resonances. Enjoy a smooth, enriching sensation that intensifies your senses and elevates your orgasm without overstimulation. Experience UltraWave Vibration, the revolutionary technology that blends deep, low-frequency vibrations with 10 powerful harmonic resonances. Powered by a linear motor, it delivers gentle yet intense stimulation, guiding you through a symphony of pleasure. Enjoy a smooth, enriching sensation that sharpens your senses and elevates your orgasm without overstimulation. UltraWave Vibration – Womanizer’s new vibration technology delivers richer, more satisfying sensations to enhance the orgasmic journey. Pleasure edges – The ergonomic shape allows for a wider range of sensations, from broad stimulation to more targeted vibrations. Silent – No distractions, just pure pleasure. 3 autopilot modes – Let Vibe guide your pleasure and enjoy one of three sensual and surprising preset vibration sequences, inspired by musical rhythms. A fantastic way to vary your play and make every orgasmic experience unique. 10 intensity levels – Whether you prefer gentle and delicate pleasure, powerful and intense stimulation, or something in between, your next orgasm is just the push of a button away. Perfectly balanced intensity levels provide the ideal setting for every mood. IPX7 waterproof – Want to dive deeper? Thanks to its IPX7 waterproof design, nothing will stop you from enjoying a long, relaxing bath, a refreshing shower, or even some poolside fun. Body-safe silicone – The surface is made from silky-soft silicone for a smooth feel against the skin. This body-safe material is free from phthalates, BPA, and latex—a true delight to the touch. USB charging port – Magnetic charging pins make recharging quick and convenient. FEATURES: Black, dark purple, sage IPX7 waterproof Run time: 240 minutes Charging time: 120 minutes Materials: Body-safe silicone Weight: 480 grams Dimensions: Length 17.1 x Width 5.4 x Height 5.7 Packaging dimensions: Length 19.3 x Width 11.2 x Height 6.8 Box includes: Womanizer Next Cotton storage pouch Additional stimulation head Quick start guide Compliance and safety information #Memasturbo sticker USB cable with magnetic charging pins (AC adapter not included)</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-vibe-lay-on-silent-vibrator-dark-blue?variant=53603350643025</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/vibe-lay-on-silent-vibrator-dark-blue-3437882.png?v=1775073027</mainImage>
		<price>106.60</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-245108</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460623797</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603385639249</ID>
		<name>BI STRONIC EMBRACE THRUSTING RABBIT PULSATORS-Black</name>
		<description>Deep impact, goosebump-worthy pleasure! The BI STRONIC EMBRACE doesn’t do things halfway – its realistic, deep thrusts hit exactly where you crave them, with an ergonomic design that ensures dual stimulation: a thrusting shaft to cater to the G-spot and a vibrating tickler for clitoral stimulation. The rhythmic back-and-forth thrusting movements imitate real life and provide lifelike sensations with every pulse. Meanwhile, powerful vibrations and a sensual, body-hugging shape embrace you fully, while the sculpted, curved tip delivers deep, targeted G-spot stimulation. Add water-based lube for even more intensity and out-of-this-world sensations. Hands-free, effortless, mind-blowingLet go and give in – two motors power 8 thrusting patterns and 6 vibration modes that can be controlled separately from each other, building the perfect rhythm to take you over the edge. And since the BI STRONIC EMBRACE does all the work, you can just lie back, relax, and let pleasure take over – completely hands-free. Always ready for your fantasiesWhether in the shower, tub, or tangled in the sheets – waterproof (IPX7), USB-C rechargeable, and made of body-friendly silicone, this love toy is always up for adventure. The ergonomic LOOP handle with a textured, ribbed, non-slip surface keeps everything secure, while the intuitive 3-button control ensures effortless navigation. Ready to play? Just press FUN. The BI STRONIC EMBRACE comes with a 25-year FUN FACTORY warranty, ensuring exceptional quality, durability, and lasting satisfaction.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/fun-factory-bi-stronic-embrace-thrusting-pulsators-black?variant=53603385639249</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/bi-stronic-embrace-thrusting-rabbit-pulsators-black-7210360.jpg?v=1775073030</mainImage>
		<price>66.11</price>
		<brand>FUN FACTORY</brand>
		<productCode>D-244303</productCode>
		<quantity>15</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4255821803378</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603385704785</ID>
		<name>BI STRONIC EMBRACE THRUSTING RABBIT PULSATORS-Rose</name>
		<description>Deep impact, goosebump-worthy pleasure! The BI STRONIC EMBRACE doesn’t do things halfway – its realistic, deep thrusts hit exactly where you crave them, with an ergonomic design that ensures dual stimulation: a thrusting shaft to cater to the G-spot and a vibrating tickler for clitoral stimulation. The rhythmic back-and-forth thrusting movements imitate real life and provide lifelike sensations with every pulse. Meanwhile, powerful vibrations and a sensual, body-hugging shape embrace you fully, while the sculpted, curved tip delivers deep, targeted G-spot stimulation. Add water-based lube for even more intensity and out-of-this-world sensations. Hands-free, effortless, mind-blowingLet go and give in – two motors power 8 thrusting patterns and 6 vibration modes that can be controlled separately from each other, building the perfect rhythm to take you over the edge. And since the BI STRONIC EMBRACE does all the work, you can just lie back, relax, and let pleasure take over – completely hands-free. Always ready for your fantasiesWhether in the shower, tub, or tangled in the sheets – waterproof (IPX7), USB-C rechargeable, and made of body-friendly silicone, this love toy is always up for adventure. The ergonomic LOOP handle with a textured, ribbed, non-slip surface keeps everything secure, while the intuitive 3-button control ensures effortless navigation. Ready to play? Just press FUN. The BI STRONIC EMBRACE comes with a 25-year FUN FACTORY warranty, ensuring exceptional quality, durability, and lasting satisfaction.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/fun-factory-bi-stronic-embrace-thrusting-pulsators-black?variant=53603385704785</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/bi-stronic-crave-thrusting-rabbit-pulsators-rose-8028129.jpg?v=1775073133</mainImage>
		<price>66.11</price>
		<brand>FUN FACTORY</brand>
		<productCode>D-244305</productCode>
		<quantity>12</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4255821803590</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603466412369</ID>
		<name>SPOT KISS ME U-SHAPED VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>Transform your intimate experience with SPOT KISS ME PINK. This innovative vibrator is designed to offer a unique combination of visual and physical stimulation, taking you to the limits of pleasure. Enjoy elevated pleasure with the KIIROO SPOT KISS ME, an ergonomic vibrator designed to offer you a unique and unforgettable experience. Its striking pink colour and innovative U-shape make it a sophisticated and elegant product, while its design is designed to perfectly adapt to the natural curves of your body, guaranteeing precise and effective stimulation in the most sensitive areas. The SPOT KISS ME has several vibration modes, allowing you to explore different intensities and rhythms until you find the perfect fit for you. Whether you prefer soft and delicate vibrations or powerful and enveloping ones, this vibrator adapts to your desires, giving you a personalized and satisfying experience with every use. Thanks to its ergonomic design, the SPOT KISS ME is incredibly easy to handle, allowing you to enjoy total control during use. Its unique U-shape is ideal for offering both internal and external stimulation, ensuring that you can experience complete pleasure, effortlessly. Made from high-quality, body-safe materials, the SPOT KISS ME is waterproof, allowing you to use it in the shower or bath, adding an extra touch of sensuality and fun. Whether you use it alone or with a partner, this vibrator is designed to accompany you in your exploration of sensuality, offering you new ways to enjoy pleasure. With the SPOT KISS ME from KIIROO, every intimate moment becomes an opportunity to discover new sensations, reaching a level of satisfaction you've never experienced before. Let yourself go and feel how technology and design come together to give you a total pleasure experience! Explore a world of sensations like never before with Kiiroo.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-spot-kiss-me-u-shaped-vibrator-pink?variant=53603466412369</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/spot-kiss-me-u-shaped-vibrator-pink-2265812.jpg?v=1775073042</mainImage>
		<price>90.90</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-242520</productCode>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8720938956454</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603572842833</ID>
		<name>VOLTA G5 CLITORAL VIBRATOR-Petrol</name>
		<description>External Vibrator VOLTA: Clit Approved.Energize your sex life with this dynamic vibrator! The VOLTA's tips flutter against the clit and labia with every rumble from its deep, powerful motor. Their rhythmic motion stimulates blood flow and increases sensitivity, making vibration more fun than ever!- Lock function for easy travel- Intuitive button interface- Charge indicator lights- Low battery warning- Non-porous and hypoallergenic- 45 minutes of play on highest speed- 4-6 hour initial charge- Designed and handcrafted in Germany- Rechargeable - Love the Earth.- Body-safe materials - Love yourself.- Waterproof - Get wet.Whether youre teasing yourself with the lightest touch of the VOLTA's tips or lying back and letting the highest setting blow you away, this vibe offers the power and versatility you crave.JUST THE TIPSLet the dynamic tips utter against the clit for incredibly powerful sensation.POWER SPLITCover your hotspots in vibration! Place one tip against the clit and one against the vaginal opening.SHARE THE FLUTTERPlace one tip on either side of the shaft and use the VOLTA as a stroker - awesome for BJs!MOTION + VIBRATION = OMGThe movement of the VOLTAs dynamic tips amplify its vibration, boost your arousal, and heighten sensitivity, letting you feel more than ever before. Explore a range of sensations from the wild percussion of the moving tips against your hotspots to classic vibration when you press the VOLTA against your body. You can even warm up with a light touch and then amp up the vibration and pressure when you want to get down to business. We recommend that you try positioning the tips in different places-on either side of the clit, against the hood, with one tip against the vaginal opening, around the labia and find your favorite way to vibe with the VOLTA.COMPACT POWERWith all the strength of a much larger toy in a lightweight, ergonomic package, the VOLTA is perfect for folks who want to add serious power to their partner sex. Love your wand, but dont want to pull it out on a first date? The lightweight, quiet VOLTA slips easily between your bodies and gives you the strong vibration you need, without interrupting your flow.FULL-BODY FUNFeeling generous? Share the FUN! The VOLTA makes a great addition to blowjobs, nipple stimulation, and more. Pro tip: using a little water-based lube, put the tips on either side of the shaft and use the Volta as a stroker.PURRING VIBRATIONChasing an orgasm that starts deep in your body and makes you see stars? Look no further. The VOLTA's powerful motor offers the rumbling, bass tone vibration that our customers love.ERGONOMIC SHAPEThe VOLTA's loop handle makes it easy to hold your toy exactly where you want it, even when your hands are covered in lube. The positioning of the raised buttons makes it simple and intuitive to try a new speed or vibration pattern without interrupting the action. Best of all, the VOLTA is shaped to feel amazing against your clit and labia no matter which angle you try.18,9 cm and Ø 4,7 cm; 193 g</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/fun-factory-volta-g5-clitoral-vibrator-petrol?variant=53603572842833</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/volta-g5-clitoral-vibrator-9938808.jpg?v=1775073046</mainImage>
		<price>66.11</price>
		<brand>FUN FACTORY</brand>
		<productCode>D-233452</productCode>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4032498806174</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603697688913</ID>
		<name>PEARL 3 G-SPOT VIBRATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>The world's most technologically advanced, award-winning G-spot vibrator just got a power and battery life upgrade. Pearl3 is a technologically advanced G-spot vibrator enabled with touch-sensitive technology. The slightly curved shape is perfect for G-spot stimulation and all types of external pleasure. The three bumps in Pearl3 stimulate the G-spot more intensely when inserted into the body. Pearl3 can connect to all Kiiroo products using the FeelConnect app so partners can feel each other in real time, no matter how far away they are. For webcam performers, Pearl3 will help them make more money as users can give control of their vibrator to their fans and use it for interactive tipping. What makes Pearl 3 different from Pearl 2? Aside from the Pearl3's vibrant new colors (purple and pink), we've improved the touch pads and extended them all the way to the tip to make the Pearl3 much more responsive to touch than its predecessors. This is ideal for play or clitoral stimulation that begins as soon as Pearl3 is inserted into the body. The silicone contour around the G-spot area on the bottom of the Pearl3 concentrates and directs vibrations directly to the G-spot area, giving the user the most pleasurable sensations. We've also added 3 hours of battery life, which is perfect for extended gaming, multiple sessions, and professional use. Who will get tired first? Product specifications Materials: ABS, silicone Finish: matte chrome for ABS, matte finish for silicone Size: 200 x 39 x 36.5mm/20 x 3.9 x 3.65cm/7.87 x 1.53 x 1.46inch Box size: 210 x 50 x 50mm/21 x 5 x 5cm/8.27 x 1.97inch Weight: 139g/4.90oz/0.30lb for device, 159g/5.60oz/0.35lb for device + USB cable Battery: Lithium-ion 540 MAH 3.7V Charge: 2 hours User time: 3 hours What you get in the box USB charging cable Authenticity card Quick Setup Manual FeelConnect App Features Available on Google Play and Apple Store. Feel your lover. Pearl3 users can use the FeelConnect app to control their partners' products remotely. They can also pair their Kiiroo products with each other through the app to feel in real time no matter the distance. Feel the webcam. Kiiroo's webcam feature allows webcam models to sync their Pearl3 with webcam platforms and receive tips for giving control of their toys to fans who are watching them. The webcam business is growing and there is a huge demand for this interactive technology among artists. Feel videos. Pearl3's vibrations sync with the movements you see on the screen, making users feel like they are in the scene. Feel Virtual Reality. Using mobile virtual reality glasses and Pearl3 users can experience high-quality adult videos filmed in 180 and 360 degrees with stereoscopic 3D views or play virtual reality porn games.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-pearl-3-g-spot-vibrator-purple?variant=53603697688913</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/pearl-3-g-spot-vibrator-purple-1016187.jpg?v=1775073084</mainImage>
		<price>106.60</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-232652</productCode>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8720256722533</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603697721681</ID>
		<name>PEARL 3 G-SPOT VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>The world's most technologically advanced, award-winning G-spot vibrator just got a power and battery life upgrade. Pearl3 is a technologically advanced G-spot vibrator enabled with touch-sensitive technology. The slightly curved shape is perfect for G-spot stimulation and all types of external pleasure. The three bumps in Pearl3 stimulate the G-spot more intensely when inserted into the body. Pearl3 can connect to all Kiiroo products using the FeelConnect app so partners can feel each other in real time, no matter how far away they are. For webcam performers, Pearl3 will help them make more money as users can give control of their vibrator to their fans and use it for interactive tipping. What makes Pearl 3 different from Pearl 2? Aside from the Pearl3's vibrant new colors (purple and pink), we've improved the touch pads and extended them all the way to the tip to make the Pearl3 much more responsive to touch than its predecessors. This is ideal for play or clitoral stimulation that begins as soon as Pearl3 is inserted into the body. The silicone contour around the G-spot area on the bottom of the Pearl3 concentrates and directs vibrations directly to the G-spot area, giving the user the most pleasurable sensations. We've also added 3 hours of battery life, which is perfect for extended gaming, multiple sessions, and professional use. Who will get tired first? Product specifications Materials: ABS, silicone Finish: matte chrome for ABS, matte finish for silicone Size: 200 x 39 x 36.5mm/20 x 3.9 x 3.65cm/7.87 x 1.53 x 1.46inch Box size: 210 x 50 x 50mm/21 x 5 x 5cm/8.27 x 1.97inch Weight: 139g/4.90oz/0.30lb for device, 159g/5.60oz/0.35lb for device + USB cable Battery: Lithium-ion 540 MAH 3.7V Charge: 2 hours User time: 3 hours What you get in the box USB charging cable Authenticity card Quick Setup Manual FeelConnect App Features Available on Google Play and Apple Store. Feel your lover. Pearl3 users can use the FeelConnect app to control their partners' products remotely. They can also pair their Kiiroo products with each other through the app to feel in real time no matter the distance. Feel the webcam. Kiiroo's webcam feature allows webcam models to sync their Pearl3 with webcam platforms and receive tips for giving control of their toys to fans who are watching them. The webcam business is growing and there is a huge demand for this interactive technology among artists. Feel videos. Pearl3's vibrations sync with the movements you see on the screen, making users feel like they are in the scene. Feel Virtual Reality. Using mobile virtual reality glasses and Pearl3 users can experience high-quality adult videos filmed in 180 and 360 degrees with stereoscopic 3D views or play virtual reality porn games.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/kiiroo-pearl-3-g-spot-vibrator-purple?variant=53603697721681</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/pearl-3-g-spot-vibrator-pink-7446086.jpg?v=1775073132</mainImage>
		<price>106.60</price>
		<brand>KIIROO</brand>
		<productCode>D-232651</productCode>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8720256722526</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603749331281</ID>
		<name>F2S MALE MASTURBATOR-Red</name>
		<description>It's time to immerse yourself in unparalleled pleasure with the F2STM male massager and masturbator. It features flexible liquid silicone ridges that easily adapt to your every move, while its two open ends ensure uninterrupted pleasure. Users can unlock two exclusive modes and use the new «Love Bridge» feature in theLELO app to discreetly connect with your partners in real time when you're not together. The product has eight modes, but with the LELO app, you can unlock two more. 8 POWERFUL PLEASURE MODES CONNECTS TO THE APP Unlock two additional modes («Finish Me O» and «Out Of Control») or use the «Love Bridge» feature in the LELOTM app to stay connected to your partner when you're apart. SELF-ADJUSTING LIQUID SILICONE STRETCHES New silicone ridges allow for airflow. This prevents air pockets from forming while providing an extra boost of stimulation. This realistic-feel material exemplifies softness, elasticity, and durability. LIQUID SILICONE This realistic-feel material exemplifies softness, elasticity, and durability. Not only does it adapt to your needs, it enhances your experience. OPEN AT BOTH ENDS AND WITH AN EXCLUSIVE DUAL MOTOR DESIGN The F2STM offers unlimited pleasure thanks to its open-ended design, which eliminates any kind of noise. Both its dual motors and modes adapt to the user's caresses, while the vibrations provide a sensation of movement. FEATURES: Materials: Biocompatible silicone, ABS plastic and aluminum alloy Finish: Smooth Size: 110 x Φ 82mm Weight: 267 g Battery: Lithium-ion 520 mAh 3.7 V Charge: up to 2 h at 5 V 520 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 520 mA 2.6 W Output: 3.7 V 440 mA 1.6 W Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons HOW TO USE YOUR F2STM AVAILABLE COLORS: • Before using it for the first time, charge your F2STM for 2 hours.• Press the «+» or the «(( ))» button to turn it on.• Press the «(( ))» button to switch between the 8 modes.• Use the «+» or the «-» button to increase or decrease the intensity.• If you just want to turn off the device, press and hold the «(( ))» button.You can also press the «+» and «-» buttons at the same time to turn it off and lock it. HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITHOUT THE LELOTM APP Before using it for the first time, charge your F2STM for 2 hours. DOWNLOAD THE IOS OR ANDROID VERSION. Press the «(( ))» button for 3 seconds to turn it on while activating Bluetooth. All LED lights will flash simultaneously to show that it is pairing via Bluetooth. Open the LELOTM app and locate the toy icon, which is located at the bottom of the screen. Locate your F2STM and select «Connect». Press and hold the button on the device. To confirm the connection, press the button on your device again. Go to «MY LELO TOYS» and select «PLAY». Choose from the 3 basic modes («Manual», «Screwing» and «Shaking») or the 2 additional advanced modes: «Finish Me O» and «Out Of Control». Use the «Love Bridge» feature to open a private chat with your partner. This way, you can exchange controls of your LELO devices that are connected to the app and bring each other to orgasm. Go to «SETTINGS» to configure the device as you wish. Click the «SAVE» button which is located at the bottom of the screen and saves the settings for when you go to use it offline Use the drop-down menu to adjust the default auto-off time to 10-20 minutes. The battery level is located in the upper left corner.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-f2sa-teal-male-masturbator-red?variant=53603749331281</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/f2s-teal-male-masturbator-red-1438121.jpg?v=1775073024</mainImage>
		<price>175.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-242819</productCode>
		<quantity>18</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029653</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603749364049</ID>
		<name>F2S MALE MASTURBATOR-Blue</name>
		<description>It's time to immerse yourself in unparalleled pleasure with the F2STM male massager and masturbator. It features flexible liquid silicone ridges that easily adapt to your every move, while its two open ends ensure uninterrupted pleasure. Users can unlock two exclusive modes and use the new «Love Bridge» feature in theLELO app to discreetly connect with your partners in real time when you're not together. The product has eight modes, but with the LELO app, you can unlock two more. 8 POWERFUL PLEASURE MODES CONNECTS TO THE APP Unlock two additional modes («Finish Me O» and «Out Of Control») or use the «Love Bridge» feature in the LELOTM app to stay connected to your partner when you're apart. SELF-ADJUSTING LIQUID SILICONE STRETCHES New silicone ridges allow for airflow. This prevents air pockets from forming while providing an extra boost of stimulation. This realistic-feel material exemplifies softness, elasticity, and durability. LIQUID SILICONE This realistic-feel material exemplifies softness, elasticity, and durability. Not only does it adapt to your needs, it enhances your experience. OPEN AT BOTH ENDS AND WITH AN EXCLUSIVE DUAL MOTOR DESIGN The F2STM offers unlimited pleasure thanks to its open-ended design, which eliminates any kind of noise. Both its dual motors and modes adapt to the user's caresses, while the vibrations provide a sensation of movement. FEATURES: Materials: Biocompatible silicone, ABS plastic and aluminum alloy Finish: Smooth Size: 110 x Φ 82mm Weight: 267 g Battery: Lithium-ion 520 mAh 3.7 V Charge: up to 2 h at 5 V 520 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 520 mA 2.6 W Output: 3.7 V 440 mA 1.6 W Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons HOW TO USE YOUR F2STM AVAILABLE COLORS: • Before using it for the first time, charge your F2STM for 2 hours.• Press the «+» or the «(( ))» button to turn it on.• Press the «(( ))» button to switch between the 8 modes.• Use the «+» or the «-» button to increase or decrease the intensity.• If you just want to turn off the device, press and hold the «(( ))» button.You can also press the «+» and «-» buttons at the same time to turn it off and lock it. HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITHOUT THE LELOTM APP Before using it for the first time, charge your F2STM for 2 hours. DOWNLOAD THE IOS OR ANDROID VERSION. Press the «(( ))» button for 3 seconds to turn it on while activating Bluetooth. All LED lights will flash simultaneously to show that it is pairing via Bluetooth. Open the LELOTM app and locate the toy icon, which is located at the bottom of the screen. Locate your F2STM and select «Connect». Press and hold the button on the device. To confirm the connection, press the button on your device again. Go to «MY LELO TOYS» and select «PLAY». Choose from the 3 basic modes («Manual», «Screwing» and «Shaking») or the 2 additional advanced modes: «Finish Me O» and «Out Of Control». Use the «Love Bridge» feature to open a private chat with your partner. This way, you can exchange controls of your LELO devices that are connected to the app and bring each other to orgasm. Go to «SETTINGS» to configure the device as you wish. Click the «SAVE» button which is located at the bottom of the screen and saves the settings for when you go to use it offline Use the drop-down menu to adjust the default auto-off time to 10-20 minutes. The battery level is located in the upper left corner.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-f2sa-teal-male-masturbator-red?variant=53603749364049</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/f2s-teal-male-masturbator-blue-3201138.jpg?v=1775073084</mainImage>
		<price>175.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-242818</productCode>
		<quantity>16</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029646</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603784032593</ID>
		<name>TOR 3 VIBRATOR RING-Black</name>
		<description>TOR™ 3 is a vibrating ring for couples that can be connected to our app. It contains more pleasure modes and intensities than the previous generation. Its soft, biocompatible silicone body adapts perfectly to all shapes and sizes, and its vibrations are transmitted to both partners to improve intimate relationships. It is compatible with the LELO application via Bluetooth. Thanks to it, you can personalize your experience to make it unique and have greater control of your device. SPECIAL FEATURES TOR™ 3 is compatible with the LELO app, allowing you to unlock more pleasure modes and experiment with different intensities to find your sweet spot. In addition to offering you a greater variety of options when playing with your TOR™ 3, the LELO app provides you with many other benefits. It is a multifunctional sexual wellness platform dedicated to human sexuality. Contains over 4,000 articles, vivid erotic literature, and valuable relationship advice. 8 POWERFUL VIBRATION MODESTOR™ 3 offers 8 vibration patterns with different intensities; from soft touches to very exciting pulses. EXTRA SOFT SILICONEHigh-quality silicone that is ultra-soft and warm to the touch so you can enjoy deeply satisfying and hygienic pleasure. CONTROLLED BY APPConnect and control your device via Bluetooth for greater pleasure. CHARACTERISTICS:Materials: Body-safe silicone and ABS plasticFinish: smoothSize: 46.7 x 22.2 x 60mmDiameter: 29mmBattery: Li-Ion 70 mAh 3.7 VCharging: Up to 2 h at 5.0 V 70 mARated power:- Input: 5V 0.35W- Output: 3.7V 0.24WUse time: up to 1.5 hoursStandby: up to 90 daysFrequency: 130HzMax level noise: 60 dBInterface: 2 buttonsOperating mode: continuous operation INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE: HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITHOUT THE LELO™ APP Before first use, charge your TORTM 3 for 2 hours. Press the + button to turn on the device. Once turned on, press the + button once to increase the intensity of the motor (there are 12 levels in total). Press the + button twice to change the engine operating pattern (Mode). Press the - button once for a long time to decrease the motor level to 0; the device will turn off. To turn it off, you can also press the - and + buttons while the device is on. HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITH THE LELO™ APP Before first use, charge your TORTM 3 for 2 hours. DOWNLOAD THE VERSION FOR IOS OR ANDROID. Press the + button to turn it on while activating Bluetooth. All LED lights flash simultaneously to show that it is pairing via Bluetooth. Open the LELOTM app and locate the toy icon at the bottom of the screen. Find your TORTM 3 and select “Connect”. Press and hold the + button on your device. To confirm the connection, press the + button on your device again. Go to “MY LELO TOYS” and select “PLAY”. Choose from three different control modes. Select “SETTINGS” to configure additional modes. If you want to save your settings for offline use, tap “SAVE” at the bottom of the screen. Use the drop-down menu to set the default auto shut-off time of 10-20 minutes. You can check the battery level in the upper left corner.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-tor-3-black-vibrator-ring?variant=53603784032593</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/tor-3-vibrator-ring-black-6971648.png?v=1775073131</mainImage>
		<price>146.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-234477</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028922</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603784065361</ID>
		<name>TOR 3 VIBRATOR RING-Blue</name>
		<description>TOR™ 3 is a vibrating ring for couples that can be connected to our app. It contains more pleasure modes and intensities than the previous generation. Its soft, biocompatible silicone body adapts perfectly to all shapes and sizes, and its vibrations are transmitted to both partners to improve intimate relationships. It is compatible with the LELO application via Bluetooth. Thanks to it, you can personalize your experience to make it unique and have greater control of your device. SPECIAL FEATURES TOR™ 3 is compatible with the LELO app, allowing you to unlock more pleasure modes and experiment with different intensities to find your sweet spot. In addition to offering you a greater variety of options when playing with your TOR™ 3, the LELO app provides you with many other benefits. It is a multifunctional sexual wellness platform dedicated to human sexuality. Contains over 4,000 articles, vivid erotic literature, and valuable relationship advice. 8 POWERFUL VIBRATION MODESTOR™ 3 offers 8 vibration patterns with different intensities; from soft touches to very exciting pulses. EXTRA SOFT SILICONEHigh-quality silicone that is ultra-soft and warm to the touch so you can enjoy deeply satisfying and hygienic pleasure. CONTROLLED BY APPConnect and control your device via Bluetooth for greater pleasure. CHARACTERISTICS:Materials: Body-safe silicone and ABS plasticFinish: smoothSize: 46.7 x 22.2 x 60mmDiameter: 29mmBattery: Li-Ion 70 mAh 3.7 VCharging: Up to 2 h at 5.0 V 70 mARated power:- Input: 5V 0.35W- Output: 3.7V 0.24WUse time: up to 1.5 hoursStandby: up to 90 daysFrequency: 130HzMax level noise: 60 dBInterface: 2 buttonsOperating mode: continuous operation INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE: HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITHOUT THE LELO™ APP Before first use, charge your TORTM 3 for 2 hours. Press the + button to turn on the device. Once turned on, press the + button once to increase the intensity of the motor (there are 12 levels in total). Press the + button twice to change the engine operating pattern (Mode). Press the - button once for a long time to decrease the motor level to 0; the device will turn off. To turn it off, you can also press the - and + buttons while the device is on. HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITH THE LELO™ APP Before first use, charge your TORTM 3 for 2 hours. DOWNLOAD THE VERSION FOR IOS OR ANDROID. Press the + button to turn it on while activating Bluetooth. All LED lights flash simultaneously to show that it is pairing via Bluetooth. Open the LELOTM app and locate the toy icon at the bottom of the screen. Find your TORTM 3 and select “Connect”. Press and hold the + button on your device. To confirm the connection, press the + button on your device again. Go to “MY LELO TOYS” and select “PLAY”. Choose from three different control modes. Select “SETTINGS” to configure additional modes. If you want to save your settings for offline use, tap “SAVE” at the bottom of the screen. Use the drop-down menu to set the default auto shut-off time of 10-20 minutes. You can check the battery level in the upper left corner.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-tor-3-black-vibrator-ring?variant=53603784065361</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/tor-3-vibrator-ring-blue-4384217.jpg?v=1775073082</mainImage>
		<price>146.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-234478</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028939</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603784098129</ID>
		<name>TOR 3 VIBRATOR RING-Violet</name>
		<description>TOR™ 3 is a vibrating ring for couples that can be connected to our app. It contains more pleasure modes and intensities than the previous generation. Its soft, biocompatible silicone body adapts perfectly to all shapes and sizes, and its vibrations are transmitted to both partners to improve intimate relationships. It is compatible with the LELO application via Bluetooth. Thanks to it, you can personalize your experience to make it unique and have greater control of your device. SPECIAL FEATURES TOR™ 3 is compatible with the LELO app, allowing you to unlock more pleasure modes and experiment with different intensities to find your sweet spot. In addition to offering you a greater variety of options when playing with your TOR™ 3, the LELO app provides you with many other benefits. It is a multifunctional sexual wellness platform dedicated to human sexuality. Contains over 4,000 articles, vivid erotic literature, and valuable relationship advice. 8 POWERFUL VIBRATION MODESTOR™ 3 offers 8 vibration patterns with different intensities; from soft touches to very exciting pulses. EXTRA SOFT SILICONEHigh-quality silicone that is ultra-soft and warm to the touch so you can enjoy deeply satisfying and hygienic pleasure. CONTROLLED BY APPConnect and control your device via Bluetooth for greater pleasure. CHARACTERISTICS:Materials: Body-safe silicone and ABS plasticFinish: smoothSize: 46.7 x 22.2 x 60mmDiameter: 29mmBattery: Li-Ion 70 mAh 3.7 VCharging: Up to 2 h at 5.0 V 70 mARated power:- Input: 5V 0.35W- Output: 3.7V 0.24WUse time: up to 1.5 hoursStandby: up to 90 daysFrequency: 130HzMax level noise: 60 dBInterface: 2 buttonsOperating mode: continuous operation INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE: HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITHOUT THE LELO™ APP Before first use, charge your TORTM 3 for 2 hours. Press the + button to turn on the device. Once turned on, press the + button once to increase the intensity of the motor (there are 12 levels in total). Press the + button twice to change the engine operating pattern (Mode). Press the - button once for a long time to decrease the motor level to 0; the device will turn off. To turn it off, you can also press the - and + buttons while the device is on. HOW TO USE YOUR PRODUCT WITH THE LELO™ APP Before first use, charge your TORTM 3 for 2 hours. DOWNLOAD THE VERSION FOR IOS OR ANDROID. Press the + button to turn it on while activating Bluetooth. All LED lights flash simultaneously to show that it is pairing via Bluetooth. Open the LELOTM app and locate the toy icon at the bottom of the screen. Find your TORTM 3 and select “Connect”. Press and hold the + button on your device. To confirm the connection, press the + button on your device again. Go to “MY LELO TOYS” and select “PLAY”. Choose from three different control modes. Select “SETTINGS” to configure additional modes. If you want to save your settings for offline use, tap “SAVE” at the bottom of the screen. Use the drop-down menu to set the default auto shut-off time of 10-20 minutes. You can check the battery level in the upper left corner.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-tor-3-black-vibrator-ring?variant=53603784098129</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/tor-3-vibrator-ring-violet-9880292.jpg?v=1775073084</mainImage>
		<price>146.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-234476</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028946</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603814113617</ID>
		<name>BULLSEYE RING VIBRATOR APP-Grey</name>
		<description>Hit the bull's-eye with the Satisfyer Bullseye. This penis ring has an elegant and timeless design, with an adjustable loop to adjust the perfect diameter for you. This makes it ideal for beginners and anyone looking for the perfect fitting penis ring. You can control it with the App Connect and it is made of body-friendly medical silicone, it is particularly flexible and soft. Thanks to the blood-congesting effect, the adjustable penis ring not only delays ejaculation, but also gives you a remarkable erection that allows you to feel every touch particularly intensely. Product information "Bullseye" More stamina due to exciting blood retention effect Individually adjustable tightness The powerful motor transmits intense vibration rhythms throughout the sexual wellness device Ideal for couples Made of super soft, skin-friendly medical-grade silicone that is smooth to the touch and extremely hygienic 15-year guarantee Body-friendly silicone Waterproof IPX7 Whisper mode Easy to clean Lithium-ion battery USB magnetic charging cable included What can the Satisfyer Bullseye offer? Here’s something to hit the spot! Seeking a penis ring that can handle anything and everything you bring to it? Check out the Bullseye! The Bullseye is an adjustable ring that allows for complete flexibility – no more struggling to find a penis ring that fits just right. This ring is perfect for beginners and experienced users alike, allowing you to explore the vast possibilities of penis rings! The Bullseye features a simple yet elegant design ideal for penile or testical stimulation. Also, let your partner benefit from experiencing additional stimulation as well when used together! This adjustable ring with a slider is truly one size fits all! What other advantages does the Satisfyer Bullseye have? With one motor and a one-touch button with 12 vibration programs, you will experience pure bliss with the Bullseye! Also, Bluetooth enabled, the Bullseye connects to the award-winning, free, Satisfyer Connect app, giving you the option to independently control the motor and customize the vibrations to perfectly suit your needs! The Bullseye is made of body-safe silicone, rechargeable, and waterproof (IPX7) rated. Hit the bullseye today!</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/satisfyer-bullseye-ring-vibrator-app-grey?variant=53603814113617</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/bullseye-ring-vibrator-app-grey-9492861.jpg?v=1775073133</mainImage>
		<price>49.95</price>
		<brand>SATISFYER</brand>
		<productCode>D-231030</productCode>
		<quantity>27</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4061504018379</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603814146385</ID>
		<name>BULLSEYE RING VIBRATOR APP-Blue</name>
		<description>Hit the bull's-eye with the Satisfyer Bullseye. This penis ring has an elegant and timeless design, with an adjustable loop to adjust the perfect diameter for you. This makes it ideal for beginners and anyone looking for the perfect fitting penis ring. You can control it with the App Connect and it is made of body-friendly medical silicone, it is particularly flexible and soft. Thanks to the blood-congesting effect, the adjustable penis ring not only delays ejaculation, but also gives you a remarkable erection that allows you to feel every touch particularly intensely. Product information "Bullseye" More stamina due to exciting blood retention effect Individually adjustable tightness The powerful motor transmits intense vibration rhythms throughout the sexual wellness device Ideal for couples Made of super soft, skin-friendly medical-grade silicone that is smooth to the touch and extremely hygienic 15-year guarantee Body-friendly silicone Waterproof IPX7 Whisper mode Easy to clean Lithium-ion battery USB magnetic charging cable included What can the Satisfyer Bullseye offer? Here’s something to hit the spot! Seeking a penis ring that can handle anything and everything you bring to it? Check out the Bullseye! The Bullseye is an adjustable ring that allows for complete flexibility – no more struggling to find a penis ring that fits just right. This ring is perfect for beginners and experienced users alike, allowing you to explore the vast possibilities of penis rings! The Bullseye features a simple yet elegant design ideal for penile or testical stimulation. Also, let your partner benefit from experiencing additional stimulation as well when used together! This adjustable ring with a slider is truly one size fits all! What other advantages does the Satisfyer Bullseye have? With one motor and a one-touch button with 12 vibration programs, you will experience pure bliss with the Bullseye! Also, Bluetooth enabled, the Bullseye connects to the award-winning, free, Satisfyer Connect app, giving you the option to independently control the motor and customize the vibrations to perfectly suit your needs! The Bullseye is made of body-safe silicone, rechargeable, and waterproof (IPX7) rated. Hit the bullseye today!</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/satisfyer-bullseye-ring-vibrator-app-grey?variant=53603814146385</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/bullseye-ring-vibrator-app-blue-4105379.jpg?v=1775073138</mainImage>
		<price>49.95</price>
		<brand>SATISFYER</brand>
		<productCode>D-231029</productCode>
		<quantity>13</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4061504018362</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603904225617</ID>
		<name>F1S V3 MALE MASTURBATOR XL-Red</name>
		<description>The F1S™ V3is an app-connected pleasure console that we've enhanced with advanced features to make your biggest fantasies come true. Now you can find it in a normal size and in a new XL size. This device has eight vibration modes, including the interactive mode with AI that we have just developed. You will be able to access this highly sensitive mode from the LELO app. TheF1S™ Made from the finest liquid silicone and featuring self-adjusting grooves, V3promises a touch of luxury that accentuates any sensation. Its two synchronized motors stimulate the penis and its nerve endings, allowing it to be used without using your hands. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone, aluminum alloy, LEXAN™ 141R Size: 144 x Φ 72mm Insertable length: 110 mm Diameter: 40 mm to 60 mm Weight: 314 g Battery: Lithium-ion 850 mAh 3.7 V Charge: 2 h at 5 V 850 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 3.75 W Output: 3.7V 1.5W Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: suction motor: 64 Hz vibration motor: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 75 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-f1s-v3-male-masturbator-red-xl?variant=53603904225617</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/f1s-v3-male-masturbator-xl-red-1681980.jpg?v=1775073013</mainImage>
		<price>212.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240511</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029677</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603904258385</ID>
		<name>F1S V3 MALE MASTURBATOR XL-Teal</name>
		<description>The F1S™ V3is an app-connected pleasure console that we've enhanced with advanced features to make your biggest fantasies come true. Now you can find it in a normal size and in a new XL size. This device has eight vibration modes, including the interactive mode with AI that we have just developed. You will be able to access this highly sensitive mode from the LELO app. TheF1S™ Made from the finest liquid silicone and featuring self-adjusting grooves, V3promises a touch of luxury that accentuates any sensation. Its two synchronized motors stimulate the penis and its nerve endings, allowing it to be used without using your hands. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone, aluminum alloy, LEXAN™ 141R Size: 144 x Φ 72mm Insertable length: 110 mm Diameter: 40 mm to 60 mm Weight: 314 g Battery: Lithium-ion 850 mAh 3.7 V Charge: 2 h at 5 V 850 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 3.75 W Output: 3.7V 1.5W Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: suction motor: 64 Hz vibration motor: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 75 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-f1s-v3-male-masturbator-red-xl?variant=53603904258385</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/f1s-v3-male-masturbator-xl-teal-6346238.jpg?v=1775073074</mainImage>
		<price>212.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240512</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029684</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603907731793</ID>
		<name>F1S V3 MALE MASTURBATOR-Red</name>
		<description>The F1S™ V3is an app-connected pleasure console that we've enhanced with advanced features to make your biggest fantasies come true. Now you can find it in a normal size and in a new XL size. This device has eight vibration modes, including the interactive mode with AI that we have just developed. You will be able to access this highly sensitive mode from the LELO app. TheF1S™ Made from the finest liquid silicone and featuring self-adjusting grooves, V3promises a touch of luxury that accentuates any sensation. Its two synchronized motors stimulate the penis and its nerve endings, allowing it to be used without using your hands. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone, aluminum alloy, LEXAN™ 141R Size: 144 x Φ 72mm Insertable length: 110 mm Diameter: 40 mm to 60 mm Weight: 314 g Battery: Lithium-ion 850 mAh 3.7 V Charge: 2 h at 5 V 850 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 3.75 W Output: 3.7V 1.5W Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: suction motor: 64 Hz vibration motor: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 75 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-f1s-v3-male-masturbator-red?variant=53603907731793</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/f1s-v3-male-masturbator-red-1265951.jpg?v=1775073084</mainImage>
		<price>212.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240510</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029622</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603907764561</ID>
		<name>F1S V3 MALE MASTURBATOR-Blue</name>
		<description>The F1S™ V3is an app-connected pleasure console that we've enhanced with advanced features to make your biggest fantasies come true. Now you can find it in a normal size and in a new XL size. This device has eight vibration modes, including the interactive mode with AI that we have just developed. You will be able to access this highly sensitive mode from the LELO app. TheF1S™ Made from the finest liquid silicone and featuring self-adjusting grooves, V3promises a touch of luxury that accentuates any sensation. Its two synchronized motors stimulate the penis and its nerve endings, allowing it to be used without using your hands. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone, aluminum alloy, LEXAN™ 141R Size: 144 x Φ 72mm Insertable length: 110 mm Diameter: 40 mm to 60 mm Weight: 314 g Battery: Lithium-ion 850 mAh 3.7 V Charge: 2 h at 5 V 850 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 3.75 W Output: 3.7V 1.5W Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: suction motor: 64 Hz vibration motor: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 75 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-f1s-v3-male-masturbator-red?variant=53603907764561</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/f1s-v3-male-masturbator-teal-7601271.jpg?v=1775073017</mainImage>
		<price>212.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240509</productCode>
		<quantity>19</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029639</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603957080401</ID>
		<name>SHANIA TRIPLE RABBIT VIBRATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>PRETTY LOVE SHANIA RABBIT VIBRATOR This uniquely textured rabbit vibrator offers mind-blowing internal and external sensations with 7 thumping and vibration settings. This toy is made with a high quality velvet silicone that provides a gorgeously, sexy, silky feel to leave you completely satisfied all night long. With an extra tongue design,this unique vibrator is sure to live up to its name and deliver climax after climax. It is the perfect bedroom addition for couples who enjoy intense, sensual, and full-on vibrational contact. FEATURES: Functions: 7 thumping functions and 7 vibration functions Powering: Magnetic USB charging Material: Silicone ABS Packaging Size(mm): 290*105*65</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/pretty-love-shania-rabbit-vibrator-multifunction-purple?variant=53603957080401</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/shania-triple-rabbit-vibrator-purple-9376735.jpg?v=1775073080</mainImage>
		<price>58.90</price>
		<brand>PRETTY LOVE</brand>
		<productCode>D-241887</productCode>
		<quantity>28</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>6959532337006</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603957113169</ID>
		<name>SHANIA TRIPLE RABBIT VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>PRETTY LOVE SHANIA RABBIT VIBRATOR This uniquely textured rabbit vibrator offers mind-blowing internal and external sensations with 7 thumping and vibration settings. This toy is made with a high quality velvet silicone that provides a gorgeously, sexy, silky feel to leave you completely satisfied all night long. With an extra tongue design,this unique vibrator is sure to live up to its name and deliver climax after climax. It is the perfect bedroom addition for couples who enjoy intense, sensual, and full-on vibrational contact. FEATURES: Functions: 7 thumping functions and 7 vibration functions Powering: Magnetic USB charging Material: Silicone ABS Packaging Size(mm): 290*105*65</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/pretty-love-shania-rabbit-vibrator-multifunction-purple?variant=53603957113169</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/shania-triple-rabbit-vibrator-pink-7812659.jpg?v=1775073038</mainImage>
		<price>58.90</price>
		<brand>PRETTY LOVE</brand>
		<productCode>D-241886</productCode>
		<quantity>33</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>6959532336986</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603969565009</ID>
		<name>STARLET 3 CLITORAL STIMULATOR-Indigo</name>
		<description>The new Womanizer Starlet 3 features the original Womanizer combined with five new vivid product colors and two more intensity levels of Pleasure Air stimulation, all while still waterproof and USB rechargeable at a reasonable price. Made for you and your body, the Starlet 3 uses a unique innovation called Pleasure Air Technology. ?Why is it so special? Your clitoris is stimulated without direct contact. Gentle air vibrations suck and massage together to provide an unprecedented orgasmic feeling. The sensual, slim design fits comfortably in your hand and becomes the perfect companion for even the most intimate moments. ? Explore six different intensity levels for the perfect pleasure for any mood you’re in. Dive deeper with the IPX7 rating, allowing you to bring your Starlet 3 into the bath or shower without fear. Because who doesn’t want to get a little wet during playtime? Key Features: Clitoral Stimulator Pleasure Air Technology 6 Intensity Levels Compact Body-Safe Waterproof Vegan-Friendly Production Magnetic Charging</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-indigo?variant=53603969565009</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-indigo-5630955.png?v=1775073049</mainImage>
		<price>69.99</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235668</productCode>
		<quantity>14</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460616409</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603969630545</ID>
		<name>STARLET 3 CLITORAL STIMULATOR-Turquoise</name>
		<description>The new Womanizer Starlet 3 features the original Womanizer combined with five new vivid product colors and two more intensity levels of Pleasure Air stimulation, all while still waterproof and USB rechargeable at a reasonable price. Made for you and your body, the Starlet 3 uses a unique innovation called Pleasure Air Technology. ?Why is it so special? Your clitoris is stimulated without direct contact. Gentle air vibrations suck and massage together to provide an unprecedented orgasmic feeling. The sensual, slim design fits comfortably in your hand and becomes the perfect companion for even the most intimate moments. ? Explore six different intensity levels for the perfect pleasure for any mood you’re in. Dive deeper with the IPX7 rating, allowing you to bring your Starlet 3 into the bath or shower without fear. Because who doesn’t want to get a little wet during playtime? Key Features: Clitoral Stimulator Pleasure Air Technology 6 Intensity Levels Compact Body-Safe Waterproof Vegan-Friendly Production Magnetic Charging</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-indigo?variant=53603969630545</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-turquoise-4947148.png?v=1775073030</mainImage>
		<price>69.99</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235664</productCode>
		<quantity>19</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460616393</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603969663313</ID>
		<name>STARLET 3 CLITORAL STIMULATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>The new Womanizer Starlet 3 features the original Womanizer combined with five new vivid product colors and two more intensity levels of Pleasure Air stimulation, all while still waterproof and USB rechargeable at a reasonable price. Made for you and your body, the Starlet 3 uses a unique innovation called Pleasure Air Technology. ?Why is it so special? Your clitoris is stimulated without direct contact. Gentle air vibrations suck and massage together to provide an unprecedented orgasmic feeling. The sensual, slim design fits comfortably in your hand and becomes the perfect companion for even the most intimate moments. ? Explore six different intensity levels for the perfect pleasure for any mood you’re in. Dive deeper with the IPX7 rating, allowing you to bring your Starlet 3 into the bath or shower without fear. Because who doesn’t want to get a little wet during playtime? Key Features: Clitoral Stimulator Pleasure Air Technology 6 Intensity Levels Compact Body-Safe Waterproof Vegan-Friendly Production Magnetic Charging</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-indigo?variant=53603969663313</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-pink-9958392.png?v=1775073032</mainImage>
		<price>69.99</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235667</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460616423</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603969696081</ID>
		<name>STARLET 3 CLITORAL STIMULATOR-Gray</name>
		<description>The new Womanizer Starlet 3 features the original Womanizer combined with five new vivid product colors and two more intensity levels of Pleasure Air stimulation, all while still waterproof and USB rechargeable at a reasonable price. Made for you and your body, the Starlet 3 uses a unique innovation called Pleasure Air Technology. ?Why is it so special? Your clitoris is stimulated without direct contact. Gentle air vibrations suck and massage together to provide an unprecedented orgasmic feeling. The sensual, slim design fits comfortably in your hand and becomes the perfect companion for even the most intimate moments. ? Explore six different intensity levels for the perfect pleasure for any mood you’re in. Dive deeper with the IPX7 rating, allowing you to bring your Starlet 3 into the bath or shower without fear. Because who doesn’t want to get a little wet during playtime? Key Features: Clitoral Stimulator Pleasure Air Technology 6 Intensity Levels Compact Body-Safe Waterproof Vegan-Friendly Production Magnetic Charging</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/womanizer-starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-indigo?variant=53603969696081</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/starlet-3-clitoral-stimulator-gray-5722582.png?v=1775073035</mainImage>
		<price>69.99</price>
		<brand>WOMANIZER</brand>
		<productCode>D-235666</productCode>
		<quantity>7</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>4251460616430</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603975004497</ID>
		<name>IDA WAVE COUPLES MASSAGER-Black</name>
		<description>SENSUAL INDEPENDENCE IDA™ Wave is a massager connected to an application and with two separate motors that will allow you to reach orgasm gradually. The insertable part rotates and, thanks to WaveMotion™ technology, also simulates the movement of the fingers to bring you overwhelming pleasure to the G-Spot. The upper part is larger and provides exquisite vibrations on the clitoris. DOUBLE THE POWER Two motors with powerful vibrations that offer internal and external stimulation. GREATER RANGE OF INTENSITIES Experience different levels of satisfaction with 10 intense pleasure modes. APP CONTROLLED Connect and control your device via Bluetooth for more pleasure. WAVEMOTION™ TECHNOLOGY Enjoy a perfect finger massage to stimulate your G-Spot. HOW TO USE TIANY™ HARMONY * Before first use, charge your IDA™ Wave for 2 hours. HOW TO USE THE PRODUCT WITHOUT THE APP Press the button to turn it on. The LEDs will flash showing the battery charge level. When the LEDs stop flashing, they will show the vibration level. Press the button to change modes. They are set to 100% intensity. Press the center button for 3 seconds to turn it off. HOW TO USE THE PRODUCT WITH THE APP Press the center button for 3 seconds to turn it on while activating Bluetooth. All LEDs will flash simultaneously to show that you are connecting with Bluetooth. Open the TIANI™ Harmony app and, once you have received the confirmation message, press the center button to confirm. When the LEDs shine without flickering, the device has been successfully connected. In case the connection fails, the product will automatically turn off after 30 seconds. Battery and vibration levels can be viewed in the app. CHARACTERISTICS Materials: Biocompatible silicone and ABS Size: 63 x 56 x 93mm Weight: 102g Battery: Li-ion 3.7 V 520 mAh Charge: 2 hours at 5.0 V 200 mA Use time: Up to 2 hours Standby: Up to 90 days Frequency: 130Hz Reducer motor frequency: 1.4 Hz Interface: 1 button Modes: 4 (default), up to 10 can be set via app</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-ida-wave-coral-couples-massager?variant=53603975004497</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/ida-wave-couples-massager-black-1514485.jpg?v=1775073077</mainImage>
		<price>168.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-232089</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028663</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603998695761</ID>
		<name>ENIGMA DOUBLE SUCTION MASSAGER-Purple</name>
		<description>We never settle, that's why we always have to go further to offer something truly from another planet. Discover ENIGMA™, a luxurious dual-action massager that offers the best of both worlds: deep clitoral and G-spot stimulation. ENIGMA™ has been created for otherworldly, sonic orgasms. The owners of an ENIGMA™ are owners of their sexual desires and are responsible for analyzing them one by one. They carry their uniqueness as their flag, from their own style to their hidden desires and pleasures, with pride, and consume them as they want, without fear of feeling different. Unlike other similar products, ENIGMA™ offers a clitoral pulsation in addition to a G-spot vibration, for an orgasm so intense that not everyone can endure. WHAT IS ENIGMA? ENIGMA™ is inspired by two of our best-selling products, SONA™ and SORAYA™ and offers the concept of the world's most luxurious hybrid pleasure. It uses sonic wave technology, which stimulates the clitoris while resonating deeply in your body, and also has an internal ergonomic stimulator that massages your G-spot, just like our SORAYA™, to lead you to a progressive orgasm that It floods you again and again. PRODUCT DESCRIPTION ENIGMA™ is a luxurious dual-action sonic massager designed to stimulate both the entire clitoris (both visible and hidden) and the G-spot, for an intense orgasm that will make you feel like you're orbiting outside of this planet. With the best sonic waves for the outer part of the clitoris and gentle pulsations on the inner part of your body, ENIGMA™ moves through the right places to give you an orgasm you will never forget. •Combines sonic waves with gentle pulsations for double the pleasure •8 vibration patterns to find that "perfect" feeling •Internal and external stimulation for amazing pleasure, just the way you like it •100% submersible and USB rechargeable to take wherever you want •Silent, but powerful and discreet, for an endless experience •1 year warranty and 10 years quality guarantee ENIGMA™ is a luxurious dual-action sonic massager designed to stimulate both the entire clitoris (both visible and hidden) and the G-spot, for an intense orgasm that will make you feel like you're orbiting outside of this planet. With the best sonic waves for the outer part of the clitoris and gentle pulsations on the inner part of your body, ENIGMA™ moves through the right places to give you an orgasm you will never forget. With the option to activate both types of stimulation, ENIGMA™ allows you to experience two different types of climaxes. It is designed for the most curious who wish to immerse themselves in new pleasures to discover. SENSONIC™ TECHNOLOGY Without making direct contact, the sonic waves offer clitoral stimulation for a deeper but gentler sensation. DOUBLE EXCITATION Simultaneously caressing the clitoris (both the part that is visible and the part that cannot be seen) and the vagina. ERGONOMIC INTERNAL STIMULATOR With a flexible internal stimulator with very powerful vibrations that stimulate your G-spot. Content ENIGMA™ USB-Charger satin cover Warranty Registration User manual Characteristics Materials: ABS/ Body-safe silicone Color: Deep Rose, Black Interface: 3 button interface Off: automatically turns off after 60 minutes Frequency: 60Hz/100Hz Battery: Li-lon 850mAh 3.7V Use time: up to 2 hours Standby time: up to 90 days Size: 100 x 50 x 185mm Insertable length: 140mm Weight (product only): 196g</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-enigma-double-suction-stimulation-purple-massager?variant=53603998695761</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/enigma-double-suction-massager-purple-2644468.jpg?v=1775073132</mainImage>
		<price>175.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-228121</productCode>
		<quantity>7</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028175</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53603998728529</ID>
		<name>ENIGMA DOUBLE SUCTION MASSAGER-Black</name>
		<description>We never settle, that's why we always have to go further to offer something truly from another planet. Discover ENIGMA™, a luxurious dual-action massager that offers the best of both worlds: deep clitoral and G-spot stimulation. ENIGMA™ has been created for otherworldly, sonic orgasms. The owners of an ENIGMA™ are owners of their sexual desires and are responsible for analyzing them one by one. They carry their uniqueness as their flag, from their own style to their hidden desires and pleasures, with pride, and consume them as they want, without fear of feeling different. Unlike other similar products, ENIGMA™ offers a clitoral pulsation in addition to a G-spot vibration, for an orgasm so intense that not everyone can endure. WHAT IS ENIGMA? ENIGMA™ is inspired by two of our best-selling products, SONA™ and SORAYA™ and offers the concept of the world's most luxurious hybrid pleasure. It uses sonic wave technology, which stimulates the clitoris while resonating deeply in your body, and also has an internal ergonomic stimulator that massages your G-spot, just like our SORAYA™, to lead you to a progressive orgasm that It floods you again and again. PRODUCT DESCRIPTION ENIGMA™ is a luxurious dual-action sonic massager designed to stimulate both the entire clitoris (both visible and hidden) and the G-spot, for an intense orgasm that will make you feel like you're orbiting outside of this planet. With the best sonic waves for the outer part of the clitoris and gentle pulsations on the inner part of your body, ENIGMA™ moves through the right places to give you an orgasm you will never forget. •Combines sonic waves with gentle pulsations for double the pleasure •8 vibration patterns to find that "perfect" feeling •Internal and external stimulation for amazing pleasure, just the way you like it •100% submersible and USB rechargeable to take wherever you want •Silent, but powerful and discreet, for an endless experience •1 year warranty and 10 years quality guarantee ENIGMA™ is a luxurious dual-action sonic massager designed to stimulate both the entire clitoris (both visible and hidden) and the G-spot, for an intense orgasm that will make you feel like you're orbiting outside of this planet. With the best sonic waves for the outer part of the clitoris and gentle pulsations on the inner part of your body, ENIGMA™ moves through the right places to give you an orgasm you will never forget. With the option to activate both types of stimulation, ENIGMA™ allows you to experience two different types of climaxes. It is designed for the most curious who wish to immerse themselves in new pleasures to discover. SENSONIC™ TECHNOLOGY Without making direct contact, the sonic waves offer clitoral stimulation for a deeper but gentler sensation. DOUBLE EXCITATION Simultaneously caressing the clitoris (both the part that is visible and the part that cannot be seen) and the vagina. ERGONOMIC INTERNAL STIMULATOR With a flexible internal stimulator with very powerful vibrations that stimulate your G-spot. Content ENIGMA™ USB-Charger satin cover Warranty Registration User manual Characteristics Materials: ABS/ Body-safe silicone Color: Deep Rose, Black Interface: 3 button interface Off: automatically turns off after 60 minutes Frequency: 60Hz/100Hz Battery: Li-lon 850mAh 3.7V Use time: up to 2 hours Standby time: up to 90 days Size: 100 x 50 x 185mm Insertable length: 140mm Weight (product only): 196g</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-enigma-double-suction-stimulation-purple-massager?variant=53603998728529</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/enigma-double-suction-massager-black-8309168.png?v=1775073135</mainImage>
		<price>175.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-228120</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028182</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604033986897</ID>
		<name>CLITORIS STIMULATOR SONA 2-Lilac</name>
		<description>LELO SONA 2 is the larger and bolder follow-up to one of LELO’s most popular products. Designed to redefine clitoral pleasure, this new generation offers stimulation through waves without direct contact, creating a sensation that feels subtle, powerful, and deeply satisfying. The Sona 2 is made to provide a broader and deeper experience thanks to its greater surface area and larger mouthpiece. Its design allows stimulation both inside and out, helping create a softer and deeper feeling during use. The wave-based stimulation is focused on the clitoris and is intended to deliver pleasure in a way that feels different from traditional direct-contact toys. Made from ultra-soft premium body-safe silicone, the SONA 2 has a smooth and comfortable feel. It includes 12 vibration modes, giving you different intensity and sensation options to explore. It is also 100% fully USB rechargeable and submersible, making it practical as well as luxurious. With dimensions of 99 x 87 x 56 mm, the LELO SONA 2 combines a bold shape, premium materials, and wave-based stimulation in one elegant device.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-clitoris-stimulator-sona-2-lilac?variant=53604033986897</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/clitoris-stimulator-sona-2-lilac-6509080.jpg?v=1775073133</mainImage>
		<price>105.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-221379</productCode>
		<quantity>22</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075027895</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604034019665</ID>
		<name>CLITORIS STIMULATOR SONA 2-Fuchsia</name>
		<description>LELO SONA 2 is the larger and bolder follow-up to one of LELO’s most popular products. Designed to redefine clitoral pleasure, this new generation offers stimulation through waves without direct contact, creating a sensation that feels subtle, powerful, and deeply satisfying. The Sona 2 is made to provide a broader and deeper experience thanks to its greater surface area and larger mouthpiece. Its design allows stimulation both inside and out, helping create a softer and deeper feeling during use. The wave-based stimulation is focused on the clitoris and is intended to deliver pleasure in a way that feels different from traditional direct-contact toys. Made from ultra-soft premium body-safe silicone, the SONA 2 has a smooth and comfortable feel. It includes 12 vibration modes, giving you different intensity and sensation options to explore. It is also 100% fully USB rechargeable and submersible, making it practical as well as luxurious. With dimensions of 99 x 87 x 56 mm, the LELO SONA 2 combines a bold shape, premium materials, and wave-based stimulation in one elegant device.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-clitoris-stimulator-sona-2-lilac?variant=53604034019665</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/clitoris-stimulator-sona-2-fuchsia-6471808.jpg?v=1775073034</mainImage>
		<price>105.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-221378</productCode>
		<quantity>15</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075027802</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604034052433</ID>
		<name>CLITORIS STIMULATOR SONA 2-Cruise lilac</name>
		<description>LELO SONA 2 is the larger and bolder follow-up to one of LELO’s most popular products. Designed to redefine clitoral pleasure, this new generation offers stimulation through waves without direct contact, creating a sensation that feels subtle, powerful, and deeply satisfying. The Sona 2 is made to provide a broader and deeper experience thanks to its greater surface area and larger mouthpiece. Its design allows stimulation both inside and out, helping create a softer and deeper feeling during use. The wave-based stimulation is focused on the clitoris and is intended to deliver pleasure in a way that feels different from traditional direct-contact toys. Made from ultra-soft premium body-safe silicone, the SONA 2 has a smooth and comfortable feel. It includes 12 vibration modes, giving you different intensity and sensation options to explore. It is also 100% fully USB rechargeable and submersible, making it practical as well as luxurious. With dimensions of 99 x 87 x 56 mm, the LELO SONA 2 combines a bold shape, premium materials, and wave-based stimulation in one elegant device.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-clitoris-stimulator-sona-2-lilac?variant=53604034052433</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/clitoris-stimulator-sona-2-cruise-lilac-3905462.jpg?v=1775073074</mainImage>
		<price>105.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-221247</productCode>
		<quantity>20</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075027871</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604082155857</ID>
		<name>ELISE 2 VIBRATOR-Lilac</name>
		<description>The pink Lelo Elise vibrator has a very harmonious design and a very exclusive finish, in line with all Lelo products. The Scandinavian vibrator manufacturer can boast of having a unique brand profile, and worldwide recognition earned with the sophistication and glamor that it imprints on each of its creations, inspired by the fashion and beauty industry. Its multiple functions and advanced features, typical of a luxury vibrator, give it infinite possibilities of use, it has all the necessary features to provide an extremely pleasant experience. Made with medical grade silicone, a material especially suitable for the manufacture of erotic toys due to its maximum compatibility. It is more hygienic due to its non-porous surface, making cleaning and maintenance easier, with maximum durability and a pleasant touch, soft as silk.Lelo Elise 2 is a very stylized vibrator, with delicately rounded shapes, with an anatomical, slightly curved body, designed to stimulate all erogenous zones. It is comfortable to hold, offering a good grip and simple access to the control buttons that will allow us to adjust all its options. Two independent vibrating devices located at the base and at the tip of the Lelo Elise are responsible for generating all its power with minimal noise, and can be combined or alternated as convenient. We can also adjust the vibration speed to our liking and we have 5 pre-programmed patterns that will make you intensely enjoy an experience of unrepeatable pleasure. It does not need batteries, it works with a battery and includes its own charger. It has an autonomy of 4 hours of continuous use and a charge indicator.Dimensions: 22 cm. long x 4.5 cm. diameter.It is presented as a real gem, with a luxurious gift box in which you will also find the charger, instructions, warranty and bag to store or transport the vibrator.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-elise-2-lilac-luxury-vibrator?variant=53604082155857</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/elise-2-vibrator-lilac-6529102.png?v=1775073074</mainImage>
		<price>175.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-195024</productCode>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022277663</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604082188625</ID>
		<name>ELISE 2 VIBRATOR-Black</name>
		<description>The pink Lelo Elise vibrator has a very harmonious design and a very exclusive finish, in line with all Lelo products. The Scandinavian vibrator manufacturer can boast of having a unique brand profile, and worldwide recognition earned with the sophistication and glamor that it imprints on each of its creations, inspired by the fashion and beauty industry. Its multiple functions and advanced features, typical of a luxury vibrator, give it infinite possibilities of use, it has all the necessary features to provide an extremely pleasant experience. Made with medical grade silicone, a material especially suitable for the manufacture of erotic toys due to its maximum compatibility. It is more hygienic due to its non-porous surface, making cleaning and maintenance easier, with maximum durability and a pleasant touch, soft as silk.Lelo Elise 2 is a very stylized vibrator, with delicately rounded shapes, with an anatomical, slightly curved body, designed to stimulate all erogenous zones. It is comfortable to hold, offering a good grip and simple access to the control buttons that will allow us to adjust all its options. Two independent vibrating devices located at the base and at the tip of the Lelo Elise are responsible for generating all its power with minimal noise, and can be combined or alternated as convenient. We can also adjust the vibration speed to our liking and we have 5 pre-programmed patterns that will make you intensely enjoy an experience of unrepeatable pleasure. It does not need batteries, it works with a battery and includes its own charger. It has an autonomy of 4 hours of continuous use and a charge indicator.Dimensions: 22 cm. long x 4.5 cm. diameter.It is presented as a real gem, with a luxurious gift box in which you will also find the charger, instructions, warranty and bag to store or transport the vibrator.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-elise-2-lilac-luxury-vibrator?variant=53604082188625</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/elise-2-vibrator-black-3969859.jpg?v=1775073020</mainImage>
		<price>175.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-195022</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022277670</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604131733841</ID>
		<name>TOR II VIBRATOR RING-Black</name>
		<description>It is the world's first ring for couples, rechargeable and waterproof, which also offers vibrations with twice the power of any other object of this style. LELO's original TOR was already the most exclusive couples ring on the market and now the Swedish designers have taken its performance even further.Created to be worn by men while making love, its extra soft silicone design comfortably adapts to all sizes, providing greater presence for him and fabulous sensations for her. In addition, its completely waterproof design has a control interface. easy to use and 6 stimulation modes. TOR 2 can also boast longevity, as its useful life is equivalent to that of about 10,000 disposable rings, which makes it a true and very profitable investment in pleasure in the short, medium and long term.As with all LELO pleasure objects, TOR 2 is designed to provide complete peace of mind in any situation and under any circumstance. Made from FDA-approved, phthalate-free PC-ABS/silicone plastic, TOR 2 provides 2 hours of virtually silent vibrations after a charge time of just 2 hours. Speed and intensity are easily regulated using an intuitive control dial, and both functions can be completely locked to ensure discreet transportation of the object at all times.Like all LELO products, TOR 2 comes in a beautiful gift box with a satin bag and a full one-year warranty.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-tor-ii-black-vibrator-ring?variant=53604131733841</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/tor-ii-vibrator-ring-black-7043735.jpg?v=1775073132</mainImage>
		<price>101.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-195033</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022271821</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604185145681</ID>
		<name>SORAYA WAVE VIBRATOR RABBIT-Black</name>
		<description>Enjoy overflowing pleasure with this luxurious bunny vibrator. Experience intense simultaneous stimulation of the clitoris and G-Spot, thanks to the patented WaveMotion™ technology, which offers you an internal massage with rocking like the caresses of the fingers of an enlightened lover, to reach a tsunami of orgasms EXCITING WAVEMOTION TECHNOLOGY ADVANTAGES Experience a tsunami of orgasms, thanks to the rocking inspired by the caresses of the fingers of enlightened lovers and a molded tip to precisely massage your G-Spot. ERGONOMIC EXTERNAL STIMULATOR With a flexible external stimulator to easily adapt to all shapes and hyper-powerful vibrations to overwhelm you with pleasure. EXTRA-SOFT SILICONE With extra-soft and biocompatible premium silicone that is as hygienic as it is pleasant to the touch. COMPLETELY SUBMERSIBLE AND RECHARGEABLE With the USB charging cable, you can take and use your SORAYA WAVE wherever you go. Plus, being submersible, it's also incredibly easy to clean. Technical characteristics: Material: ABS and biocompatible silicone Size: 220 x 75 x 44mm Insertable length: 110mm Weight: 186g Battery: Li-Ion 850mAh 3.7V Charging time: 2 hours at 5.0V 750mA Use time: Up to 2 hours Standby time: Up to 90 days Frequency: 120HZ Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-soraya-wave-vibrator-rabbit-black?variant=53604185145681</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/soraya-wave-vibrator-rabbit-black-5412381.png?v=1775073016</mainImage>
		<price>220.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-223492</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028151</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604185178449</ID>
		<name>SORAYA WAVE VIBRATOR RABBIT-Purple</name>
		<description>Enjoy overflowing pleasure with this luxurious bunny vibrator. Experience intense simultaneous stimulation of the clitoris and G-Spot, thanks to the patented WaveMotion™ technology, which offers you an internal massage with rocking like the caresses of the fingers of an enlightened lover, to reach a tsunami of orgasms EXCITING WAVEMOTION TECHNOLOGY ADVANTAGES Experience a tsunami of orgasms, thanks to the rocking inspired by the caresses of the fingers of enlightened lovers and a molded tip to precisely massage your G-Spot. ERGONOMIC EXTERNAL STIMULATOR With a flexible external stimulator to easily adapt to all shapes and hyper-powerful vibrations to overwhelm you with pleasure. EXTRA-SOFT SILICONE With extra-soft and biocompatible premium silicone that is as hygienic as it is pleasant to the touch. COMPLETELY SUBMERSIBLE AND RECHARGEABLE With the USB charging cable, you can take and use your SORAYA WAVE wherever you go. Plus, being submersible, it's also incredibly easy to clean. Technical characteristics: Material: ABS and biocompatible silicone Size: 220 x 75 x 44mm Insertable length: 110mm Weight: 186g Battery: Li-Ion 850mAh 3.7V Charging time: 2 hours at 5.0V 750mA Use time: Up to 2 hours Standby time: Up to 90 days Frequency: 120HZ Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-soraya-wave-vibrator-rabbit-black?variant=53604185178449</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/soraya-wave-vibrator-rabbit-purple-3262755.png?v=1775073073</mainImage>
		<price>220.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-223491</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075027840</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53604185211217</ID>
		<name>SORAYA WAVE VIBRATOR RABBIT-Midnight blue</name>
		<description>Enjoy overflowing pleasure with this luxurious bunny vibrator. Experience intense simultaneous stimulation of the clitoris and G-Spot, thanks to the patented WaveMotion™ technology, which offers you an internal massage with rocking like the caresses of the fingers of an enlightened lover, to reach a tsunami of orgasms EXCITING WAVEMOTION TECHNOLOGY ADVANTAGES Experience a tsunami of orgasms, thanks to the rocking inspired by the caresses of the fingers of enlightened lovers and a molded tip to precisely massage your G-Spot. ERGONOMIC EXTERNAL STIMULATOR With a flexible external stimulator to easily adapt to all shapes and hyper-powerful vibrations to overwhelm you with pleasure. EXTRA-SOFT SILICONE With extra-soft and biocompatible premium silicone that is as hygienic as it is pleasant to the touch. COMPLETELY SUBMERSIBLE AND RECHARGEABLE With the USB charging cable, you can take and use your SORAYA WAVE wherever you go. Plus, being submersible, it's also incredibly easy to clean. Technical characteristics: Material: ABS and biocompatible silicone Size: 220 x 75 x 44mm Insertable length: 110mm Weight: 186g Battery: Li-Ion 850mAh 3.7V Charging time: 2 hours at 5.0V 750mA Use time: Up to 2 hours Standby time: Up to 90 days Frequency: 120HZ Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-soraya-wave-vibrator-rabbit-black?variant=53604185211217</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/soraya-wave-vibrator-rabbit-midnight-blue-4875161.jpg?v=1775073088</mainImage>
		<price>220.90</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-223490</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028144</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53650856149329</ID>
		<name>ROTATING REMOTE CONTROL PROSTATE MASSAGER</name>
		<description>Experience a unique and deep pleasure experience with the Addicted Toys rotating prostate massager, a device designed to offer precise, powerful, and completely personalized stimulation. This massager combines advanced technology with an anatomical design that adapts perfectly to the male body, providing intense stimulation of the P-spot (prostate) and perineum. Thanks to its super-powerful motor and innovative rotating head, this stimulator offers an enveloping internal massage sensation that reproduces the circular motion of a manual massage, reaching the prostate with precision and increasing the intensity of each vibration. Its 10 vibration modes allow you to adjust the experience to your liking, from gentle pulsations to deep waves of pleasure that will bring you to the most intense climax. The wireless remote control adds a touch of fun and convenience, allowing you to manage the functions without interrupting the moment. It's ideal for couples play, allowing your partner to control the intensity and pace of pleasure, or for enjoying it solo with total freedom. Made with ultra-smooth medical silicone and high-quality ABS, this massager is body-safe, phthalate-free, and completely flexible, ensuring comfortable, safe, and pleasurable insertion. Its smooth, velvety surface offers a silky, very pleasant feel, while its ergonomic design adapts perfectly to the male anatomy for effective P-spot stimulation. FEATURES: Wireless remote control. 10 powerful and varied vibration modes. Super-powerful motor with rotating head. Precise stimulation of the P-spot (prostate). Measurements: Total length 132 mm / Insertable length 110 mm / Width 105 - 160 mm. Made in Medical-grade silicone and high-quality ABS. Body-safe, phthalate-free material. Ultra-soft, flexible, and silky-smooth silicone. Waterproof. USB rechargeable. The Addicted Toys rotating prostate massager is the perfect combination of technology, design, and power. Ideal for beginners or experienced users, it offers intense and precise stimulation of the P-spot that will take you to a new level of pleasure and well-being. Addicted Toys is a brand that breaks taboos to offer pleasure, hygiene, and sexual well-being products without filters or complexes. Its philosophy is based on facilitating safe and pleasurable body exploration, combining functional design, high-quality materials, and affordable prices. The brand is committed to a free, inclusive, and limitless sexuality, where the user is in control of their experience. Each product is designed to integrate naturally into your intimate routine, ensuring not only pleasure but also safety, hygiene, and confidence.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/addicted-toys-rotating-prostate-massager-remote-control?variant=53650856149329</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/addicted-toys-rotating-remote-control-prostate-massager-luvmechanics-6008253.png?v=1778150729</mainImage>
		<price>41.28</price>
		<brand>ADDICTED TOYS</brand>
		<productCode>D-244706</productCode>
		<quantity>50</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8435565959722</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53650889212241</ID>
		<name>ROWAN INCLUSIVE COUPLE VIBRATOR</name>
		<description>Discover a new way to connect and share pleasure with the Rowan inclusive couples vibrator from Intense, an innovative stimulator designed to adapt to all body types, genders, and orientations. Its ergonomic design and advanced vibration technology make it the perfect companion to enjoy as a couple or alone, offering an intimate, sensual, and completely inclusive experience. Rowan has 10 vibration and stimulation modes, created to explore different intensities, rhythms, and sensations. From gentle pulsations to deep vibrations, its powerful motor distributes energy evenly to deliver simultaneous pleasure to different areas of the body. Its ergonomic and flexible shape adapts perfectly to curves, allowing for multiple uses: stimulation of the clitoris, penis, perineum, or even the G-spot. Designed with the concept of inclusive pleasure in mind, this vibrator breaks gender barriers and adapts to all bodies, inviting each person to explore their own unique way of enjoying themselves. It is ideal for couples looking for new experiences, as it can be used during penetration or foreplay, intensifying sensations and improving sexual connection. FEATURES: Inclusive vibrator designed for all genders. 10 vibration and stimulation modes. Ergonomic and flexible shape that adapts to every anatomy. Perfect for use as a couple or solo. Made of super-soft medical silicone and high-quality materials. Body-safe and phthalate-free material. Resistant to Water. Charging via USB Rowan Intense's inclusive couples vibrator redefines intimacy with a modern, open, and versatile approach. Designed to offer pleasure without labels, it combines elegance, power, and softness in a single device designed for all bodies. Enjoy an authentic connection experience, without rules and without limits. INTENSE is a brand specializing in modern erotic toys, designed to offer pleasure with style, innovation, and safety. Their products stand out for their use of high-quality materials, such as super-soft, phthalate-free silicone, always with body care in mind. With ergonomic designs, powerful, rechargeable motors, and versatile functions, they combine technology, comfort, and sensuality in every creation.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/intense-rowan-inclusive-couple-vibrator?variant=53650889212241</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/intense-rowan-inclusive-couple-vibrator-luvmechanics-2507631.png?v=1778150729</mainImage>
		<price>37.15</price>
		<brand>INTENSE</brand>
		<productCode>D-244717</productCode>
		<quantity>25</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8435565959869</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698719154513</ID>
		<name>SMART WAND 2</name>
		<description>THE MOST POWERFUL STIMULATION AND THE MOST RELAXING MASSAGE. When stress evaporates with the world's most desired full-body massager, it's time to experience everything its 10 vibration modes can do to your erogenous zones. Enjoy hours of massage and pleasure with just one charge. Material: Silicone, PC, ABS Size: 304 x 80 x 60mm Weight: 383g Battery: Li-Ion 1200/1050mA 3.7V Charge: 2.5h at 5.0V 750mA CHARACTERISTICS LONG LASTING CHARGE ADVANTAGES Up to 4 hours of use per charge and 10 vibration modes to enjoy a total massage. ELEGANT DESIGN WITH INCREDIBLE POWER Easy to use, with an intensity that can be as gentle as it is overwhelming. EXTRA-SOFT SILICONE With extra-soft and biocompatible premium silicone. COMPLETELY SUBMERSIBLE AND USB RECHARGEABLE To use it in the bath or shower and take it wherever you want. In use: up to 4 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: 80Hz Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-smart-wand-2-bordeaux?variant=53698719154513</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-smart-wand-2-luvmechanics-6938913.jpg?v=1778150712</mainImage>
		<price>164.45</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-222676</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075027789</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698719187281</ID>
		<name>ORA 3 ORAL SEX STIMULATOR</name>
		<description>LELO's sophisticated oral sex simulator made an impression in 2014, winning international awards at the Cannes Lions and A-Design Awards, both for best Product Design. ORA™ 3 is the perfected version that now has a larger, faster and firmer tongue and more precisely replicates the desired stimulation of an almost perfect, almost infinite cunnilingus. TONGUE WITH BIGGER, FIRMER, MORE FLEXIBLE ROTATION So that nothing gets in the way of the most intense climax With 12 vibration patterns to simulate the most pleasurable oral sex EXTRA-SOFT SILICONE With extra-soft and biocompatible premium silicone PREMOTION™ TECHNOLOGY With a firmer and more precise movement, for 25% faster oral sex simulation Elevate your intimate moments to new sensual heights with ORA™ 3, the award-winning oral sex simulator, now perfected. And delight in the honeys of an illustrated and almost eternal cunnilingus, thanks to its power and improved tongue. 12 powerful vibration modes A faster tongue for total pleasure Extra-soft premium silicone 100% submersible and USB rechargeable 1 year warranty and 10 years quality guarantee What is PreMotion™ technology? ORA™ 3 comes with PreMotion™ technology to offer you a more realistic oral sex simulation, thanks to a firmer, more precise movement and 25% more speed. SPECIFICATIONS Material: Silicone, PC, ABS. Size: 83.5 x 88 x 43.5mm Weight: 130g Battery: Li-Ion 420mA 3.7V Charge: 2 hours at 5.0V 400mA In use: up to 1 hour Standby: 90 days Frequency: 100Hz Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-ora-3-lilac-oral-sex-stimulator?variant=53698719187281</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-ora-3-oral-sex-stimulator-luvmechanics-7511273.jpg?v=1778150713</mainImage>
		<price>147.93</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-222030</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075027970</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698748514641</ID>
		<name>INA 3 RABBIT LUXURY VIBRATOR</name>
		<description>INA™ 3 is back stronger than ever: your favorite rampant bunny has a new look. Explore your body with this beautiful dual-action massager, which has 30% more power, a greater range of intensities and no less than ten different vibration settings that will stimulate your G-spot and clitoris like never before. Get intimate with yourself and your body and watch as you discover a new, deeper balance. GREATER RANGE OF INTENSITIES We have increased the range of intensities to 10 because we know that satisfaction has no limits. EXTRA POWER 30% more power for more intense and deeper vibrations. LONGER LASTING BATTERY With a longer lasting battery so you can enjoy hours and hours of pleasure. RECHARGEABLE more powerful, quieter 10 VERSATILE VIBRATION MODES from gentle hum to extreme vibration DESIGNED FOR YOUR PLEASURE double action: releases the G Spot and facilitates 100% clitoral orgasm SUBMERSIBLE perfect for the bath and shower LONG-TERM CHARGE more pleasure, for longer ULTRA-SOFT SILICONE High-quality silicone that is ultra-soft to the touch We have improved the acclaimed rampant bunny. Made with the softest biocompatible silicone and in three stunning new colors, INA™ 3 is the perfect dual-action massager that will give you a happy ending. With ten exquisite vibration modes, internal G-spot stimulation and external clitoral stimulation, enjoy stimulating power and release all your pent-up inhibitions. Materials: biocompatible silicone, ABS Size: 200 x 65 x 45mm Insertable length: 110mm Weight: 150g Battery: Li-lon 520mA 3.7V Charge: 2 h at 5.0V 500mAh Use time: up to 2 hours Standby: 90 days Frequency: 60Hz Interface: 4 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-ina-3-green-rabbit-vibrator-luxury-seaweed?variant=53698748514641</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-ina-3-rabbit-luxury-vibrator-luvmechanics-2919833.jpg?v=1778150726</mainImage>
		<price>147.93</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-229372</productCode>
		<quantity>3</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028304</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698748580177</ID>
		<name>BILLY ANAL VIBRATOR 2</name>
		<description>The wait is over. After 4 years, we are proud to present to you the latest male pleasure product: it is Billy™ 2 and it is here to offer the best orgasms to all men. And finally, the taboo on anal stimulation has been broken and the market for prostate massagers has expanded to many more users. Not only have men discovered the health benefits of massage, but they are also experiencing more intense orgasms. Billy™ 2 is not only ideal for connoisseurs, it is also perfect for beginners. Gentlemen, join the club. Enter the unlimited society of male health and pleasure with Billy 2. This unique prostate massager has 8 vibration modes and even more power than its predecessor, in addition to being USB rechargeable and completely submersible. Are you ready to discover the grail of the most intense orgasms? ERGONOMIC DESIGN Designed to precisely massage the prostate and with the ideal diameter for easy and comfortable insertion COMPLETELY SUBMERSIBLE Ideal for the bath or shower 8 POWERFUL VIBRATION MODES With improved functionality to unleash male pleasures EXTRA SOFT SILICONE It comes in a curved shape and soft silicone, with a safety ring at the base that ensures maximum pleasure. Materials: Silicone and ABS plastic Matte finish Size: 174 x 35 x 29mm/6.9 x 1.4 x 1.1in Diameter: ⌀29mm/1.1in Insertable length: 100mm/3.9in Weight:92g/3.2oz Battery: Li-Ion 500mAh 3.7V Charging time: 2hrs at 5.0V 500mA Usage time:Up to 4 hours Standby:Up to 90 days Frequency:120Hz Max. noise level: 50dB Interface: - 4 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-billy-anal-vibraor-2-black?variant=53698748580177</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-billy-anal-vibrator-2-luvmechanics-4673306.jpg?v=1778150711</mainImage>
		<price>123.14</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-222027</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075024337</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698762473809</ID>
		<name>LYLA 2 MASSAGER EGG</name>
		<description>The World's Most Advanced Oval Shaped Massager with Remote Control. Lyla™ 2 is the most advanced oval-shaped massager in the world today, it can be used both externally and internally, and allows you to enjoy a wide variety of exciting sensations. Featuring for the first time LELO's SenseMotion™ technology and a remote control with a range of up to 12 meters, the intense vibration modes are easily controlled with a simple tilt of the remote. At the same time, a discreet motor inside the remote control will replicate the vibrations of Lyla™ 2 allowing you to feel in your hand the vibrations that your partner is experiencing. Amazingly quiet, 100% waterproof and rechargeable, and designed with soft and delicate silicone, Lyla™ 2 offers a wide range of possibilities in couples games.The new Design edition includes some really interesting improvements such as: 50% more power, with less noise. Expanded remote control vibration range (x3). Intelligent memory chip to avoid vibration interruptions caused by environmental interference. Possibility of controlling the vibration patterns with or without the remote control, from the toy itself. Content: Lyla™ 2 Pink Pleasure Object. Remote control. Charger. 2 AAA batteries. Badge Brooch. Satin bag. 1 year LELO warranty</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-lyla-2-insignia-design-edition-purple-massager-egg?variant=53698762473809</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-lyla-2-massager-egg-luvmechanics-4014348.jpg?v=1778150727</mainImage>
		<price>131.40</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-195037</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022275911</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698762506577</ID>
		<name>TIANI 3 MASSAGER</name>
		<description>The most exclusive massager for couples to be carried by the woman when making love Tiani™ 3 is the new and improved version of the original Red Dot Design Award-winning couples massager, worn by women during lovemaking. Its improved vibration with double the power provides sensations directed especially to the clitoris, while its soft silicone design provides incomparable pleasure and supreme comfort.Submersible, rechargeable and with remote control, Tiani™ 3 is LELO's new design to share multiple orgasms with your partner. The luxurious couples massager to wear while making love New soft silicone design with 100% more powerful motor Remote control with SenseMotion™ technology 8 stimulation modes (6 standard and 2 created with the remote control) 100% submersible and rechargeable 10-year quality guarantee Tiani 3 comes in the award-winning LELO box with its country-specific charger, a satin storage bag, free single-dose lubricant and a full 1-year warranty.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-insignia-tiani-3-fuchsia-massager?variant=53698762506577</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-tiani-3-massager-luvmechanics-3578632.png?v=1778150717</mainImage>
		<price>139.66</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-196741</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022279346</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698765816145</ID>
		<name>MONA WAVE VIBRATOR</name>
		<description>Surrender to waves of intense sensations with the first G-Spot stimulator that emulates the best massages. The voluptuous shape and the revolutionary “come here” movement will make MONA WAVE™ not only take you to the limits of pleasure, but also reveal an unsuspected world of sensations. All in an elegant 100% silicone, rechargeable and submersible design so you can enjoy its 10 vibration modes wherever you want. Designed specifically for the G-Spot Swings like the fingers of enlightened lovers 10 vibration modes with adjustable speeds 100% submersible and rechargeable (2 hours of continuous use) 100% ultra-soft and biocompatible silicone design Insertable length: 11cm Furthermore, MONA WAVE™ is presented in an elegant gift box that contains a luxurious satin pouch for storage, as well as a charger, user manual and the full 1-year LELO warranty and 10-Year quality guarantee.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-mona-wave-vibrator-purple?variant=53698765816145</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-mona-wave-vibrator-luvmechanics-1496194.png?v=1778150726</mainImage>
		<price>131.41</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-202511</productCode>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075021350</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53698765881681</ID>
		<name>SWITCH WANDA DOUBLE STIMULATION VIBRATOR</name>
		<description>LELO SWITCH™ is a double-ended vibrator designed for versatile pleasure. Crafted with a seamless, ergonomic silhouette, it features ultra-smooth sensory ridges for enhanced nerve stimulation and tactile feedback. It connects to the LELO™ app, allowing remote control and customizable settings. Compact, stylish, and functional, it's ideal for those looking for more from their pleasure products, offering the best of both worlds in one sleek design. - DOUBLE STIMULATION: A double-ended vibrator with two built-in motors allows for seamless switching between external massage and internal stimulation, for double the pleasure every time. - SENSORY RIBS: Ultra-smooth, textured ridges increase sensitivity by stimulating more nerve endings and increasing blood flow for deeper, fuller sensations. - SMART APP CONNECTIVITY: Connect to the LELO™ app for remote control, custom vibration patterns, and partner play—pleasure at your pace or theirs. - ULTRA-SOFT BODY-SAFE SILICONE: Made with premium silicone that's soft and warm to the touch. FEATURES: Materials: Body-safe silicone, ABS plastic Finish: Smooth Size: 217 x 64 x 43 mm Insertable length: 83 mm Weight: 167 g ±10% Battery: Lithium 3.7V, 1000 mAh Charging time: Less than 2 hours Power: Input 5V 1000 mA (5 W) / Output 3.7V 800 mA (2.96 W) Use time: Up to 2 hours (automatically shuts off every 20 minutes) Standby mode: Up to 90 days Top motor frequency: 100 Hz Handle motor frequency: 93 Hz Maximum noise level: less than 63 dB Interface: 3 buttons and 2 LED lights</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-switch-vibrator-wanda-double-stimulation-lilac?variant=53698765881681</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-switch-wanda-double-stimulation-vibrator-luvmechanics-1610324.jpg?v=1778150728</mainImage>
		<price>164.45</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-244536</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260278</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702416564561</ID>
		<name>SURFER 2 VIBRATING ANAL PLUG-Black</name>
		<description>SURFER™ 2 is a vibrating anal massager perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couple play. It is made of a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, being fully waterproof and USB rechargeable to ensure a total satisfaction experience in any setting. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your pleasure possibilities. SURFER™ 2 offers you: 4 UNIQUE MODES + 2 APP EXCLUSIVE MODES + 8 INTENSITIES: Because there is no such thing as too much or too little satisfaction. FULLY WATERPROOF AND USB RECHARGEABLE: LELO SURFER™ 2 is a 100% waterproof vibrator, made of a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight. Perfect for the bath, shower or jacuzzi. MEDIUM SIZE FOR ALL LEVELS OF EXPERIENCE: Vibrating anal massager perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couple play. CHARACTERISTICS: Modes: 4 unique modes + 2 App-exclusive modes Intensities: 8 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for bath, shower or jacuzzi Size: Medium LELO has established itself as the leading luxury pleasure brand, renowned for its design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is more than just a pleasure toy brand; it's a self-care movement for those who understand that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of unashamed ecstasy, the joy of discovering all the wonders of your own body, empowering our customers with the confidence for a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-surfer-2-unisex-anal-vibrating-plug-black?variant=53702416564561</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-surfer-2-vibrating-anal-plug-luvmechanics-1089780.jpg?v=1778150716</mainImage>
		<price>99.17</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245469</productCode>
		<quantity>9</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260551</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702416597329</ID>
		<name>SURFER 2 VIBRATING ANAL PLUG-Purple</name>
		<description>SURFER™ 2 is a vibrating anal massager perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couple play. It is made of a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, being fully waterproof and USB rechargeable to ensure a total satisfaction experience in any setting. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your pleasure possibilities. SURFER™ 2 offers you: 4 UNIQUE MODES + 2 APP EXCLUSIVE MODES + 8 INTENSITIES: Because there is no such thing as too much or too little satisfaction. FULLY WATERPROOF AND USB RECHARGEABLE: LELO SURFER™ 2 is a 100% waterproof vibrator, made of a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight. Perfect for the bath, shower or jacuzzi. MEDIUM SIZE FOR ALL LEVELS OF EXPERIENCE: Vibrating anal massager perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couple play. CHARACTERISTICS: Modes: 4 unique modes + 2 App-exclusive modes Intensities: 8 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for bath, shower or jacuzzi Size: Medium LELO has established itself as the leading luxury pleasure brand, renowned for its design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is more than just a pleasure toy brand; it's a self-care movement for those who understand that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of unashamed ecstasy, the joy of discovering all the wonders of your own body, empowering our customers with the confidence for a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-surfer-2-unisex-anal-vibrating-plug-black?variant=53702416597329</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-surfer-2-vibrating-anal-plug-luvmechanics-5568900.jpg?v=1778150716</mainImage>
		<price>99.17</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245468</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260568</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702438879569</ID>
		<name>SONA 3 SONIC CLITORAL MASSAGER-Purple</name>
		<description>SONA™ 3 Cruise is a sonic clitoral stimulator featuring Cruise Control™ technology to ensure consistent intensity throughout use. It offers ten pleasure modes and the ability to change intensity levels with maximum comfort thanks to the new SmoothRise™ technology. Its ultra-soft silicone surface provides exceptional comfort during use, making it perfect for uninterrupted, intense pleasure. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app to unlock two exclusive modes as well as the Love Bridge feature, designed for long-distance connections. SONA™ 3 Cruise offers you: SENSONIC™ AND CRUISE CONTROL™ TECHNOLOGIES: SenSonic™ technology uses subtle sonic waves to stimulate the clitoris intensely without direct contact. Cruise Control™ technology automatically increases intensity when the device is pressed firmly against the body, ensuring controlled and consistent pleasure at all times. SMOOTHRISE™ TECHNOLOGY: A gradual transition between different intensity modes for maximum comfort. APP CONNECTIVITY: Unlock two additional modes (“Finish Me O” and “Out Of Control”) or use the Love Bridge feature in the LELO™ app to stay connected with your partner when you are apart. ULTRA-SOFT SILICONE: Surrender to exceptionally delicate, ultra-soft silicone that adapts to your body’s curves and mimics the natural softness of skin. TWELVE POWERFUL PLEASURE MODES: The device includes ten modes with different intensity levels, giving you maximum control over sensations. Connect to the LELO™ app to unlock two additional modes. FEATURES: Materials: body-safe silicone and ABS plastic Finish: soft-touch Size: 112 x 51 x 55 mm Weight: 128 g Battery: lithium-ion 520 mAh 3.7 V Charging: up to 2 hours at 5.0 V 520 mA Rated power: Input: 5 V 520 mA 2.6 W Output: 3.7 V 220 mA 0.8 W Usage time: up to 2 hours Standby time: 90 days Maximum noise level: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons LELO has established itself as the leading luxury pleasure brand in the market for design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is more than just a pleasure toy brand; it is a self-care movement for those who know that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of shame-free ecstasy and the joy of discovering all the wonders of your own body, empowering our customers with the confidence to enjoy a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-sona-3-cruise-sonic-clitoral-massager-plum?variant=53702438879569</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-sona-3-sonic-clitoral-massager-luvmechanics-3203260.jpg?v=1778150723</mainImage>
		<price>139.66</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245062</productCode>
		<quantity>16</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029837</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702496321873</ID>
		<name>GIZI LITE 2-IN-1 VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>The Snail Vibe GIZI Lite is designed to explore and enhance G-spot pleasure through perfectly synchronized dual stimulation. Its shape allows you to find the ideal depth while vibrations caress both vaginal and clitoral areas at the same time, creating a balanced, immersive, and deeply satisfying experience. Thanks to its ergonomic design and dual motors, the GIZI Lite delivers precise, targeted stimulation exactly where it’s needed most. Crafted from premium body-safe silicone, its soft and flexible texture adapts naturally to the body, ensuring comfort and control during every session. The SVibe GIZI Lite features 5 vibration speeds, allowing you to tailor the intensity to your personal preference. Its splashproof design supports carefree use, while the plug-in charging system provides simple and reliable power. Perfect for discovering new sensations or enhancing familiar pleasure, the GIZI Lite turns every experience into a deeper, more connected, and nuanced moment. An invitation to explore pleasure with greater precision, awareness, and satisfaction. FEATURES: Dual G-spot and clitoral stimulation Dual motors for synchronized, targeted pleasure 5 vibration speeds Ergonomic shape for a natural fit Soft, body-safe silicone material Plug-in charging Splashproof design MEASUREMENTS: Insertable length: from 120 mm / 4.7” to 35 mm / 1.4” Weight: 300 g / 0.7 lb</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/snail-vibe-gizi-lite-dual-g-spot-clitoral-pink-vibrator?variant=53702496321873</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/snail-vibe-gizi-lite-dual-vibrator-luvmechanics-4509066.jpg?v=1778150717</mainImage>
		<price>45.45</price>
		<brand>SNAIL VIBE</brand>
		<productCode>D-245138</productCode>
		<quantity>11</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8720615765683</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702496354641</ID>
		<name>GIZI LITE 2-IN-1 VIBRATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>The Snail Vibe GIZI Lite is designed to explore and enhance G-spot pleasure through perfectly synchronized dual stimulation. Its shape allows you to find the ideal depth while vibrations caress both vaginal and clitoral areas at the same time, creating a balanced, immersive, and deeply satisfying experience. Thanks to its ergonomic design and dual motors, the GIZI Lite delivers precise, targeted stimulation exactly where it’s needed most. Crafted from premium body-safe silicone, its soft and flexible texture adapts naturally to the body, ensuring comfort and control during every session. The SVibe GIZI Lite features 5 vibration speeds, allowing you to tailor the intensity to your personal preference. Its splashproof design supports carefree use, while the plug-in charging system provides simple and reliable power. Perfect for discovering new sensations or enhancing familiar pleasure, the GIZI Lite turns every experience into a deeper, more connected, and nuanced moment. An invitation to explore pleasure with greater precision, awareness, and satisfaction. FEATURES: Dual G-spot and clitoral stimulation Dual motors for synchronized, targeted pleasure 5 vibration speeds Ergonomic shape for a natural fit Soft, body-safe silicone material Plug-in charging Splashproof design MEASUREMENTS: Insertable length: from 120 mm / 4.7” to 35 mm / 1.4” Weight: 300 g / 0.7 lb</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/snail-vibe-gizi-lite-dual-g-spot-clitoral-pink-vibrator?variant=53702496354641</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/snail-vibe-gizi-lite-dual-vibrator-luvmechanics-2629242.jpg?v=1778150716</mainImage>
		<price>45.45</price>
		<brand>SNAIL VIBE</brand>
		<productCode>D-245139</productCode>
		<quantity>13</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>8720615765690</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702553862481</ID>
		<name>LINX DUAL CHANNEL ELECTRO STIMULATOR-Black</name>
		<description>The ElectraStim Linx is a next-generation dual-channel electro stimulator designed to deliver powerful, precise, and fully customizable electrical stimulation. Released to celebrate ElectraStim’s 25 years of innovation, Linx represents a major step forward in modern electro play by combining premium hardware with advanced connectivity. Linx can be used as a stand-alone device with no smartphone required, offering over 20 built-in stimulation patterns and 99 intensity levels per channel for highly precise control. Each channel operates independently, allowing tailored stimulation across multiple accessories and configurations. When connected via Bluetooth to the free ElectraStim Linx App, users unlock an extensive range of interactive play modes and advanced customization options. From detailed control over intensity and frequency to dynamic modes that respond to movement, sound, or audio tracks, Linx delivers one of the most versatile electrostimulation experiences available. Integrated remote play functionality allows control to be shared securely with a partner from anywhere in the world, making long-distance electro play seamless and accessible. With USB-C rechargeable battery, high-contrast OLED display, and user-updatable firmware, the ElectraStim Linx is built to evolve and deliver long-term performance. FEATURES: Dual-channel electro stimulator 20+ built-in stimulation patterns for stand-alone use 99 independent intensity levels per channel Bluetooth connectivity with free ElectraStim Linx App 10 interactive stimulation and control modes Integrated remote control play Symmetrical bi-phasic output for smoother stimulation OLED display with tactile physical controls USB-C rechargeable battery (up to 6 hours of use) User-updatable firmware for future features WHAT’S INCLUDED? 1 × ElectraStim Linx Electro Stimulator (EM220) 1 × Zipped protective storage case 1 × Detachable belt clip 4 × Self-adhesive ElectraPads 2 × Connecting cables with 2 mm pin connectors 1 × USB-C charging cable 1 × Free extended warranty card 1 × Quick-start guide</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/electrastim-linx-dual-channel-electro-stimulator-app-remote-control?variant=53702553862481</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/electrastim-linx-dual-channel-electro-stimulator-luvmechanics-6150015.jpg?v=1778150727</mainImage>
		<price>395.86</price>
		<brand>ELECTRASTIM</brand>
		<productCode>D-245140</productCode>
		<quantity>7</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>0609224032745</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702591938897</ID>
		<name>MINI RECHARGEABLE WAND-Black</name>
		<description>Looking for a high-quality vibrator at a premium price? You’ve found it. This mini wand from Rocks Off proves that great things come in small (and affordable) packages. With 16 exciting settings and a sleek, body-safe design, it delivers everything you need for relaxation, pleasure, or both. Whether it’s your first toy or your new favorite, this is vibration without compromise. FEATURES: 16 functions Water-resistant Precision tip Targeted stimulation of pleasure points Powerful vibrations Pocket-sized, ideal for travel 90 minutes of charging for up to 60 minutes of playtime Rechargeable – USB cable included Material: Silicone / ABS plastic Dimensions: Width: 30 mm / Height: 115 mm Rocks Off has over 20 years of experience creating innovative, high-quality adult toys. We design and manufacture our products in-house, ensuring exceptional standards without a premium price tag. Every item begins as a concept in our Kettering office, and we never rely on rebranding or repackaging. This approach has made us one of the most trusted brands in the industry. Our diverse range includes powerful vibrators, discreet couple’s toys, vibrating anal plugs, and anal toys, all made from medical-grade, body-safe silicone.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-16-functions-black-tulip?variant=53702591938897</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-luvmechanics-9335928.jpg?v=1778244908</mainImage>
		<price>22.31</price>
		<brand>ROCKS-OFF</brand>
		<productCode>D-244963</productCode>
		<quantity>20</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702591971665</ID>
		<name>MINI RECHARGEABLE WAND-Red</name>
		<description>Looking for a high-quality vibrator at a premium price? You’ve found it. This mini wand from Rocks Off proves that great things come in small (and affordable) packages. With 16 exciting settings and a sleek, body-safe design, it delivers everything you need for relaxation, pleasure, or both. Whether it’s your first toy or your new favorite, this is vibration without compromise. FEATURES: 16 functions Water-resistant Precision tip Targeted stimulation of pleasure points Powerful vibrations Pocket-sized, ideal for travel 90 minutes of charging for up to 60 minutes of playtime Rechargeable – USB cable included Material: Silicone / ABS plastic Dimensions: Width: 30 mm / Height: 115 mm Rocks Off has over 20 years of experience creating innovative, high-quality adult toys. We design and manufacture our products in-house, ensuring exceptional standards without a premium price tag. Every item begins as a concept in our Kettering office, and we never rely on rebranding or repackaging. This approach has made us one of the most trusted brands in the industry. Our diverse range includes powerful vibrators, discreet couple’s toys, vibrating anal plugs, and anal toys, all made from medical-grade, body-safe silicone.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-16-functions-black-tulip?variant=53702591971665</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-luvmechanics-1456775.jpg?v=1778150732</mainImage>
		<price>22.31</price>
		<brand>ROCKS-OFF</brand>
		<productCode>D-244965</productCode>
		<quantity>22</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702592004433</ID>
		<name>MINI RECHARGEABLE WAND-Pink</name>
		<description>Looking for a high-quality vibrator at a premium price? You’ve found it. This mini wand from Rocks Off proves that great things come in small (and affordable) packages. With 16 exciting settings and a sleek, body-safe design, it delivers everything you need for relaxation, pleasure, or both. Whether it’s your first toy or your new favorite, this is vibration without compromise. FEATURES: 16 functions Water-resistant Precision tip Targeted stimulation of pleasure points Powerful vibrations Pocket-sized, ideal for travel 90 minutes of charging for up to 60 minutes of playtime Rechargeable – USB cable included Material: Silicone / ABS plastic Dimensions: Width: 30 mm / Height: 115 mm Rocks Off has over 20 years of experience creating innovative, high-quality adult toys. We design and manufacture our products in-house, ensuring exceptional standards without a premium price tag. Every item begins as a concept in our Kettering office, and we never rely on rebranding or repackaging. This approach has made us one of the most trusted brands in the industry. Our diverse range includes powerful vibrators, discreet couple’s toys, vibrating anal plugs, and anal toys, all made from medical-grade, body-safe silicone.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-16-functions-black-tulip?variant=53702592004433</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-luvmechanics-4770999.jpg?v=1778150732</mainImage>
		<price>22.31</price>
		<brand>ROCKS-OFF</brand>
		<productCode>D-244966</productCode>
		<quantity>28</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702592037201</ID>
		<name>MINI RECHARGEABLE WAND-Purple</name>
		<description>Looking for a high-quality vibrator at a premium price? You’ve found it. This mini wand from Rocks Off proves that great things come in small (and affordable) packages. With 16 exciting settings and a sleek, body-safe design, it delivers everything you need for relaxation, pleasure, or both. Whether it’s your first toy or your new favorite, this is vibration without compromise. FEATURES: 16 functions Water-resistant Precision tip Targeted stimulation of pleasure points Powerful vibrations Pocket-sized, ideal for travel 90 minutes of charging for up to 60 minutes of playtime Rechargeable – USB cable included Material: Silicone / ABS plastic Dimensions: Width: 30 mm / Height: 115 mm Rocks Off has over 20 years of experience creating innovative, high-quality adult toys. We design and manufacture our products in-house, ensuring exceptional standards without a premium price tag. Every item begins as a concept in our Kettering office, and we never rely on rebranding or repackaging. This approach has made us one of the most trusted brands in the industry. Our diverse range includes powerful vibrators, discreet couple’s toys, vibrating anal plugs, and anal toys, all made from medical-grade, body-safe silicone.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-16-functions-black-tulip?variant=53702592037201</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/rocks-off-mini-rechargeable-wand-luvmechanics-6709263.jpg?v=1778150733</mainImage>
		<price>22.31</price>
		<brand>ROCKS-OFF</brand>
		<productCode>D-244964</productCode>
		<quantity>17</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702613926225</ID>
		<name>TIANI TWIST COUPLES VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>This couples vibrating massager is perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couples play. It is made from a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, making it completely waterproof and USB rechargeable to guarantee a fully satisfying experience in any environment. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your possibilities for pleasure. This ergonomic design offers you: 8 UNIQUE MODES + 2 EXCLUSIVE APP MODES + 16 INTENSITIES: Because there’s no such thing as too much or too little satisfaction. ULTRA-SOFT SENSORY RIDGES: Intensifies every caress for both partners, transmitting sensations to a greater number of nerve endings. FULLY WATERPROOF AND USB RECHARGEABLE: A 100% waterproof couples vibrator, perfect for the bath, shower, or jacuzzi. FEATURES: Modes: 8 unique modes + 2 exclusive App modes Intensities: 16 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for bath, shower, or jacuzzi Size: Adjustable for couples LELO has established itself as the luxury pleasure brand, leading the market in design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is not just a pleasure toy brand; it is a self-care movement aimed at those who know that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of ecstasy without shame, the pleasure of discovering all the wonders of one's own body, empowering our customers with the confidence that allows them a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-tiani-twist-couples-vibrator-soft-pink?variant=53702613926225</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-tiani-twist-couples-vibrator-luvmechanics-2538528.jpg?v=1778150717</mainImage>
		<price>98.34</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245684</productCode>
		<quantity>15</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260933</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702613958993</ID>
		<name>TIANI TWIST COUPLES VIBRATOR-Blue</name>
		<description>This couples vibrating massager is perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couples play. It is made from a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, making it completely waterproof and USB rechargeable to guarantee a fully satisfying experience in any environment. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your possibilities for pleasure. This ergonomic design offers you: 8 UNIQUE MODES + 2 EXCLUSIVE APP MODES + 16 INTENSITIES: Because there’s no such thing as too much or too little satisfaction. ULTRA-SOFT SENSORY RIDGES: Intensifies every caress for both partners, transmitting sensations to a greater number of nerve endings. FULLY WATERPROOF AND USB RECHARGEABLE: A 100% waterproof couples vibrator, perfect for the bath, shower, or jacuzzi. FEATURES: Modes: 8 unique modes + 2 exclusive App modes Intensities: 16 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for bath, shower, or jacuzzi Size: Adjustable for couples LELO has established itself as the luxury pleasure brand, leading the market in design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is not just a pleasure toy brand; it is a self-care movement aimed at those who know that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of ecstasy without shame, the pleasure of discovering all the wonders of one's own body, empowering our customers with the confidence that allows them a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-tiani-twist-couples-vibrator-soft-pink?variant=53702613958993</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-tiani-twist-couples-vibrator-luvmechanics-4585610.jpg?v=1778150715</mainImage>
		<price>98.34</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245685</productCode>
		<quantity>17</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260926</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702658195793</ID>
		<name>MIA 3 PERSONAL VIBRATOR-Black</name>
		<description>MIA™ 3 is a discreet personal vibrator designed for ultimate pleasure while on the go. Its nearly silent vibrations ensure privacy wherever you are. Its ultra-soft material feels warm to the touch, enhancing the sensory experience. The strongest feature of MIA™ 3 is its compact size, so it fits easily into handbags, purses, or suitcases, making it convenient to carry and ensuring pleasure is always within reach. It is discreet because it looks like a regular lipstick, which makes it simple and perfect for travel. Available in three colors, this compact vibrator is ideal for spontaneous pleasure, fitting perfectly even into the smallest bags. FEATURES: Material: ABS, food-grade siliconeFinish: MatteSize: 22 x 22 x 111 mm / 0.87 x 0.87 x 4.37 inWeight: 36 g / 1.27 ozBattery: Li-Ion 70 mAh 3.7 VCharging: up to 2 h at 5.0 V 70 mARated power: Input: 5V 0.35W / Output: 3.7 V 0.4 WUsage time: up to 1.5 hStandby: 90 daysFrequency: 130 HzMax noise level: less than 60 dBInterface: 2 buttons HOW TO USE: Before first use, charge your MIA™ 3 for 2 hours.The interface of your MIA™ 3 may be locked.Press and hold the + and – buttons for 3 seconds.Press the “+” button briefly to turn it on.Double-click the “+” or “-” button to switch between 8 modes.Press the “-” button briefly at level 1 to turn it off.Press and hold the “-” button at other levels to turn it off.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-mia-3-personal-vibrator-black?variant=53702658195793</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-mia-3-personal-vibrator-luvmechanics-5130111.jpg?v=1778245140</mainImage>
		<price>81.81</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240095</productCode>
		<quantity>9</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029707</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702658228561</ID>
		<name>MIA 3 PERSONAL VIBRATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>MIA™ 3 is a discreet personal vibrator designed for ultimate pleasure while on the go. Its nearly silent vibrations ensure privacy wherever you are. Its ultra-soft material feels warm to the touch, enhancing the sensory experience. The strongest feature of MIA™ 3 is its compact size, so it fits easily into handbags, purses, or suitcases, making it convenient to carry and ensuring pleasure is always within reach. It is discreet because it looks like a regular lipstick, which makes it simple and perfect for travel. Available in three colors, this compact vibrator is ideal for spontaneous pleasure, fitting perfectly even into the smallest bags. FEATURES: Material: ABS, food-grade siliconeFinish: MatteSize: 22 x 22 x 111 mm / 0.87 x 0.87 x 4.37 inWeight: 36 g / 1.27 ozBattery: Li-Ion 70 mAh 3.7 VCharging: up to 2 h at 5.0 V 70 mARated power: Input: 5V 0.35W / Output: 3.7 V 0.4 WUsage time: up to 1.5 hStandby: 90 daysFrequency: 130 HzMax noise level: less than 60 dBInterface: 2 buttons HOW TO USE: Before first use, charge your MIA™ 3 for 2 hours.The interface of your MIA™ 3 may be locked.Press and hold the + and – buttons for 3 seconds.Press the “+” button briefly to turn it on.Double-click the “+” or “-” button to switch between 8 modes.Press the “-” button briefly at level 1 to turn it off.Press and hold the “-” button at other levels to turn it off.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-mia-3-personal-vibrator-black?variant=53702658228561</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-mia-3-personal-vibrator-luvmechanics-5124234.jpg?v=1778150713</mainImage>
		<price>81.81</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240094</productCode>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029721</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702658261329</ID>
		<name>MIA 3 PERSONAL VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>MIA™ 3 is a discreet personal vibrator designed for ultimate pleasure while on the go. Its nearly silent vibrations ensure privacy wherever you are. Its ultra-soft material feels warm to the touch, enhancing the sensory experience. The strongest feature of MIA™ 3 is its compact size, so it fits easily into handbags, purses, or suitcases, making it convenient to carry and ensuring pleasure is always within reach. It is discreet because it looks like a regular lipstick, which makes it simple and perfect for travel. Available in three colors, this compact vibrator is ideal for spontaneous pleasure, fitting perfectly even into the smallest bags. FEATURES: Material: ABS, food-grade siliconeFinish: MatteSize: 22 x 22 x 111 mm / 0.87 x 0.87 x 4.37 inWeight: 36 g / 1.27 ozBattery: Li-Ion 70 mAh 3.7 VCharging: up to 2 h at 5.0 V 70 mARated power: Input: 5V 0.35W / Output: 3.7 V 0.4 WUsage time: up to 1.5 hStandby: 90 daysFrequency: 130 HzMax noise level: less than 60 dBInterface: 2 buttons HOW TO USE: Before first use, charge your MIA™ 3 for 2 hours.The interface of your MIA™ 3 may be locked.Press and hold the + and – buttons for 3 seconds.Press the “+” button briefly to turn it on.Double-click the “+” or “-” button to switch between 8 modes.Press the “-” button briefly at level 1 to turn it off.Press and hold the “-” button at other levels to turn it off.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-mia-3-personal-vibrator-black?variant=53702658261329</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-mia-3-personal-vibrator-luvmechanics-4388752.jpg?v=1778150714</mainImage>
		<price>81.81</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240096</productCode>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029738</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702678380881</ID>
		<name>SIRI 3 CLITORIS MASSAGER-Lilac</name>
		<description>SIRI™ 3 is a sound-activated clitoral massager that responds to music frequencies in real time and transmits them to the clitoris in the form of pleasant vibrations thanks to SoundSense technology. It has eight powerful pleasure modes and two built-in microphones that allow both sound recognition and noise cancellation to be precise, thus eliminating noise. unwanted ambient noise. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: smooth Size: 96 x 45 x 34 mm Weight: 172 g Battery: 420 mAh 3.7 V lithium-ion battery Charge: up to 2 hours at 5.0 V 500 mA Nominal power: Input: 5 V 420mA 2.1 W Output: 3.7 V 200mA 0.74 W Use time: up to 2h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface: 4 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-siri-3-clitoris-massager-calm-lavender?variant=53702678380881</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-siri-3-clitoris-massager-luvmechanics-2835307.jpg?v=1778150718</mainImage>
		<price>131.40</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240507</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029165</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702678413649</ID>
		<name>SIRI 3 CLITORIS MASSAGER-Green</name>
		<description>SIRI™ 3 is a sound-activated clitoral massager that responds to music frequencies in real time and transmits them to the clitoris in the form of pleasant vibrations thanks to SoundSense technology. It has eight powerful pleasure modes and two built-in microphones that allow both sound recognition and noise cancellation to be precise, thus eliminating noise. unwanted ambient noise. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: smooth Size: 96 x 45 x 34 mm Weight: 172 g Battery: 420 mAh 3.7 V lithium-ion battery Charge: up to 2 hours at 5.0 V 500 mA Nominal power: Input: 5 V 420mA 2.1 W Output: 3.7 V 200mA 0.74 W Use time: up to 2h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface: 4 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-siri-3-clitoris-massager-calm-lavender?variant=53702678413649</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-siri-3-clitoris-massager-luvmechanics-4087870.jpg?v=1778150720</mainImage>
		<price>131.40</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240500</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029172</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702678446417</ID>
		<name>SIRI 3 CLITORIS MASSAGER-Lavander</name>
		<description>SIRI™ 3 is a sound-activated clitoral massager that responds to music frequencies in real time and transmits them to the clitoris in the form of pleasant vibrations thanks to SoundSense technology. It has eight powerful pleasure modes and two built-in microphones that allow both sound recognition and noise cancellation to be precise, thus eliminating noise. unwanted ambient noise. FEATURES: Materials: biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: smooth Size: 96 x 45 x 34 mm Weight: 172 g Battery: 420 mAh 3.7 V lithium-ion battery Charge: up to 2 hours at 5.0 V 500 mA Nominal power: Input: 5 V 420mA 2.1 W Output: 3.7 V 200mA 0.74 W Use time: up to 2h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 93 Hz Max. level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface: 4 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-siri-3-clitoris-massager-calm-lavender?variant=53702678446417</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-siri-3-clitoris-massager-luvmechanics-5861822.jpg?v=1778150717</mainImage>
		<price>131.40</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-240508</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029158</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702693847377</ID>
		<name>LIV™ 3 G-SPOT STIMULATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>We are thrilled to introduce LIV™ 3, our latest G-spot vibrator that perfectly complements the body and is designed to enhance its customers' self-love journey. With its refined design and personalized pleasure options through the LELO app, LIV™ 3 is sure to catch your eye. Elegantly encased in ultra-soft silicone for absolute comfort, LIV™ 3 perfectly fits all anatomies, providing easy access to powerful G-spot stimulation. With eight unique settings and a redesigned shape, this vibrator delivers deep, precise massages for profound orgasmic release. Connecting your LIV™ 3 to the LELO app via Bluetooth unlocks two additional modes, offering an enhanced, customizable experience tailored to your preferences. The product is set with a default auto-off time of 20 minutes, which can be easily adjusted via the app. Features: Materials: Biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: Smooth Size: 169 x 35 x 42 mm Insertable length: 100 mm Weight: 93 g Battery: Li-ion 420 mAh 3.7 V Charging: up to 2 h at 5 V 420 mA Nominal power: • Input: 5 V 420 mA 2.1 W • Output: 3.7 V 600 mA 2.22 W Use time: up to 2 h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 100 Hz Max. noise level: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-liv%E2%84%A2-3-g-spot-stimulator-violet?variant=53702693847377</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-liv-3-g-spot-stimulator-luvmechanics-9566765.jpg?v=1778150724</mainImage>
		<price>81.81</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-241848</productCode>
		<quantity>7</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029783</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702693880145</ID>
		<name>LIV™ 3 G-SPOT STIMULATOR-Blue</name>
		<description>We are thrilled to introduce LIV™ 3, our latest G-spot vibrator that perfectly complements the body and is designed to enhance its customers' self-love journey. With its refined design and personalized pleasure options through the LELO app, LIV™ 3 is sure to catch your eye. Elegantly encased in ultra-soft silicone for absolute comfort, LIV™ 3 perfectly fits all anatomies, providing easy access to powerful G-spot stimulation. With eight unique settings and a redesigned shape, this vibrator delivers deep, precise massages for profound orgasmic release. Connecting your LIV™ 3 to the LELO app via Bluetooth unlocks two additional modes, offering an enhanced, customizable experience tailored to your preferences. The product is set with a default auto-off time of 20 minutes, which can be easily adjusted via the app. Features: Materials: Biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: Smooth Size: 169 x 35 x 42 mm Insertable length: 100 mm Weight: 93 g Battery: Li-ion 420 mAh 3.7 V Charging: up to 2 h at 5 V 420 mA Nominal power: • Input: 5 V 420 mA 2.1 W • Output: 3.7 V 600 mA 2.22 W Use time: up to 2 h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 100 Hz Max. noise level: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-liv%E2%84%A2-3-g-spot-stimulator-violet?variant=53702693880145</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-liv-3-g-spot-stimulator-luvmechanics-1814641.jpg?v=1778150726</mainImage>
		<price>81.81</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-241849</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029776</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702705906001</ID>
		<name>GIGI™ 3 G-SPOT VIBRATOR-Pink</name>
		<description>We've redesigned the shape of our latest G-spot vibrator, the GIGI™ 3, to fit perfectly and offer unrivaled customization and control. The newest model features a smooth silicone exterior, ensuring a comfortable experience as well as greater control over its multiple pleasure modes. From the LELO app, you can access two additional modes and customize your user experience. It's time to discover precise G-spot stimulation and different, exciting sensations with the new GIGI™ 3. GIGI™ GIGI™ 3 is compatible with the LELO app, allowing users to unlock more pleasure modes and experiment with different intensities to find their sweet spot. As well as giving you a wider range of options when playing with your GIGI™ 3, the LELO app provides you with many other benefits. It is a multi-functional sexual wellness platform dedicated to human sexuality. It features over 4,000 articles, vivid erotic literature and valuable relationship advice. The product is set with a default auto-off time of 20 minutes, which can be easily adjusted through the app. FEATURES: Materials: Biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: Smooth Size: 163 x 35 x 42 mm Insertable length: 90 mm Weight: 87 g Battery: Li-ion 420 mAh 3.7 V Charging: up to 2 h at 5 V 420 mA Nominal power: Input: 5 V 420 mA 2.1 W Output: 3.7 V 600 mA 2.22 W Use time: up to 2 h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 100 Hz Max. noise level: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-gigi%E2%84%A2-3-g-spot-vibrator-pink?variant=53702705906001</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-gigi-3-g-spot-vibrator-luvmechanics-3408201.jpg?v=1778150714</mainImage>
		<price>123.13</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-241850</productCode>
		<quantity>6</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029769</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702705938769</ID>
		<name>GIGI™ 3 G-SPOT VIBRATOR-Blue</name>
		<description>We've redesigned the shape of our latest G-spot vibrator, the GIGI™ 3, to fit perfectly and offer unrivaled customization and control. The newest model features a smooth silicone exterior, ensuring a comfortable experience as well as greater control over its multiple pleasure modes. From the LELO app, you can access two additional modes and customize your user experience. It's time to discover precise G-spot stimulation and different, exciting sensations with the new GIGI™ 3. GIGI™ GIGI™ 3 is compatible with the LELO app, allowing users to unlock more pleasure modes and experiment with different intensities to find their sweet spot. As well as giving you a wider range of options when playing with your GIGI™ 3, the LELO app provides you with many other benefits. It is a multi-functional sexual wellness platform dedicated to human sexuality. It features over 4,000 articles, vivid erotic literature and valuable relationship advice. The product is set with a default auto-off time of 20 minutes, which can be easily adjusted through the app. FEATURES: Materials: Biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish: Smooth Size: 163 x 35 x 42 mm Insertable length: 90 mm Weight: 87 g Battery: Li-ion 420 mAh 3.7 V Charging: up to 2 h at 5 V 420 mA Nominal power: Input: 5 V 420 mA 2.1 W Output: 3.7 V 600 mA 2.22 W Use time: up to 2 h Standby: 90 days Frequency: 100 Hz Max. noise level: less than 60 dB Interface: 3 buttons</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-gigi%E2%84%A2-3-g-spot-vibrator-pink?variant=53702705938769</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-gigi-3-g-spot-vibrator-luvmechanics-2976038.jpg?v=1778150715</mainImage>
		<price>123.13</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-241852</productCode>
		<quantity>7</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075029745</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702741524817</ID>
		<name>LOKI WAVE 2 PROSTATE MASSAGER-Blue</name>
		<description>Here is the new generation of our legendary vibrating prostate stimulator. LOKI Wave™ 2 moves back and forth with a finger-like internal massaging motion for sweeping prostate stimulation. Experience unprecedented orgasmic satisfaction thanks to the 12 pleasure modes powered by 2 motors and its flexible and ergonomic internal massager arm that we have completely redesigned. Feel the intensity inside you and enjoy the pleasure with the stylish LOKI Wave™ 2. 12 POWERFUL VIBRATION MODES: LOKI Wave™ 2 offers 12 vibration patterns with different intensities; from soft touches to very exciting pulses. EXTRA SOFT SILICONE : High-quality silicone that is ultra-soft and warm to the touch so you can enjoy a deeply gratifying and hygienic pleasure at the same time. USB RECHARGEABLE AND 100% WATERPROOF TO IPX7 STANDARD : Enjoy unlimited climaxes anytime, anywhere, including in the bath or shower. GREATER POWER FOR MORE INTENSE PLEASURE : With 2 motors that focus precisely on the prostate and perineum to achieve much more explosive climaxes. CHARACTERISTICS: Materials: biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish : smooth Size : 91 x 42 x 196mm Insertable length : 100 mm Weight : 196g Battery : lithium 850 mAh 3.7 V Charge : up to 2 hours at 5.0 V 750 mA Use time : up to 2 hours Standby : up to 90 days Frequency: 122Hz Max level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface : 5 buttons INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE: Before first use, charge your LOKI Wave™ 2 for 2 hours. The device interface may be blocked. Hold + and - for 3 seconds. Press the On/O button to turn it on. Press the or V buttons to cycle through the 12 modes. Use the + or - buttons to increase or decrease the intensity. Press and hold the On/O button to turn it off.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-loki-wave-2-prostate-massager-blue?variant=53702741524817</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-loki-wave-2-prostate-massager-luvmechanics-5795641.jpg?v=1778150711</mainImage>
		<price>180.99</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-232968</productCode>
		<quantity>9</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028984</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702741557585</ID>
		<name>LOKI WAVE 2 PROSTATE MASSAGER-Lilac</name>
		<description>Here is the new generation of our legendary vibrating prostate stimulator. LOKI Wave™ 2 moves back and forth with a finger-like internal massaging motion for sweeping prostate stimulation. Experience unprecedented orgasmic satisfaction thanks to the 12 pleasure modes powered by 2 motors and its flexible and ergonomic internal massager arm that we have completely redesigned. Feel the intensity inside you and enjoy the pleasure with the stylish LOKI Wave™ 2. 12 POWERFUL VIBRATION MODES: LOKI Wave™ 2 offers 12 vibration patterns with different intensities; from soft touches to very exciting pulses. EXTRA SOFT SILICONE : High-quality silicone that is ultra-soft and warm to the touch so you can enjoy a deeply gratifying and hygienic pleasure at the same time. USB RECHARGEABLE AND 100% WATERPROOF TO IPX7 STANDARD : Enjoy unlimited climaxes anytime, anywhere, including in the bath or shower. GREATER POWER FOR MORE INTENSE PLEASURE : With 2 motors that focus precisely on the prostate and perineum to achieve much more explosive climaxes. CHARACTERISTICS: Materials: biocompatible silicone and ABS plastic Finish : smooth Size : 91 x 42 x 196mm Insertable length : 100 mm Weight : 196g Battery : lithium 850 mAh 3.7 V Charge : up to 2 hours at 5.0 V 750 mA Use time : up to 2 hours Standby : up to 90 days Frequency: 122Hz Max level Noise: less than 60 dB Interface : 5 buttons INSTRUCTIONS FOR USE: Before first use, charge your LOKI Wave™ 2 for 2 hours. The device interface may be blocked. Hold + and - for 3 seconds. Press the On/O button to turn it on. Press the or V buttons to cycle through the 12 modes. Use the + or - buttons to increase or decrease the intensity. Press and hold the On/O button to turn it off.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-loki-wave-2-prostate-massager-blue?variant=53702741557585</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-loki-wave-2-prostate-massager-luvmechanics-3518610.jpg?v=1778150711</mainImage>
		<price>180.99</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-232969</productCode>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350075028977</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702752403793</ID>
		<name>MONA 2 VIBRATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>It can be said that this beautiful medium-sized vibrator has curves where they need to be: thanks to its ergonomic shapes, it is capable of causing sensations of an intensity and fullness that would seem impossible in a vibrator of this size. Its six stimulation modes also help to ensure that such a delicious exploration adventure lasts over time without ever losing interest. Also designed to stimulate the G-spot and the clitoris in very different ways, MONA 2 is ideal for those who, alone or as a couple, want to take their sensuality a little further and satisfy the desire to live an incomparable experience inside.As with all LELO pleasure objects, MONA 2 is designed to provide intense physical joy and absolute spiritual peace in any situation and under any circumstance.Made from FDA-approved, phthalate-free PC-ABS/silicone plastic, MONA provides 4 hours of virtually silent vibrations after a charge time of just 2 hours.Speed and intensity are easily regulated using an intuitive control dial, and both functions can be completely locked to ensure discreet transportation of the object at all times.Additionally, MONA comes in an elegant gift box containing a luxurious satin pouch for storage, plus a charger, user manual and full 1-year LELO warranty.Now the new MONA 2 includes new improvements compared to the previous version: It has a unique contour to reach the G-spot, transmitting pleasure where it counts most. Double the power in each of its 6 vibration patterns. Its engines have been improved to take your pleasure to the limit. Now fully submersible for more versatile use. So you can enjoy it in the bath or shower and also clean it more easily. Rechargeable, silent and ready to travel. Total lock with discreet and pleasant vibrations. Body safe and very comfortable. Made with FDA silicone with extremely soft coating. Unrivaled quality and guarantee. It has a 1-year Lelo warranty for your maximum peace of mind. Size: 20 x 3.5cm.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-mona-2-vibrator-fuchsia?variant=53702752403793</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-mona-2-vibrator-luvmechanics-6641161.jpg?v=1778150724</mainImage>
		<price>131.41</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-195011</productCode>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022277625</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702752436561</ID>
		<name>MONA 2 VIBRATOR-Red</name>
		<description>It can be said that this beautiful medium-sized vibrator has curves where they need to be: thanks to its ergonomic shapes, it is capable of causing sensations of an intensity and fullness that would seem impossible in a vibrator of this size. Its six stimulation modes also help to ensure that such a delicious exploration adventure lasts over time without ever losing interest. Also designed to stimulate the G-spot and the clitoris in very different ways, MONA 2 is ideal for those who, alone or as a couple, want to take their sensuality a little further and satisfy the desire to live an incomparable experience inside.As with all LELO pleasure objects, MONA 2 is designed to provide intense physical joy and absolute spiritual peace in any situation and under any circumstance.Made from FDA-approved, phthalate-free PC-ABS/silicone plastic, MONA provides 4 hours of virtually silent vibrations after a charge time of just 2 hours.Speed and intensity are easily regulated using an intuitive control dial, and both functions can be completely locked to ensure discreet transportation of the object at all times.Additionally, MONA comes in an elegant gift box containing a luxurious satin pouch for storage, plus a charger, user manual and full 1-year LELO warranty.Now the new MONA 2 includes new improvements compared to the previous version: It has a unique contour to reach the G-spot, transmitting pleasure where it counts most. Double the power in each of its 6 vibration patterns. Its engines have been improved to take your pleasure to the limit. Now fully submersible for more versatile use. So you can enjoy it in the bath or shower and also clean it more easily. Rechargeable, silent and ready to travel. Total lock with discreet and pleasant vibrations. Body safe and very comfortable. Made with FDA silicone with extremely soft coating. Unrivaled quality and guarantee. It has a 1-year Lelo warranty for your maximum peace of mind. Size: 20 x 3.5cm.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-mona-2-vibrator-fuchsia?variant=53702752436561</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-mona-2-vibrator-luvmechanics-3929087.jpg?v=1778150723</mainImage>
		<price>131.41</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-195010</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350022277601</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702790512977</ID>
		<name>BOOMERANG DOUBLE ENDED VIBRATOR-Orange</name>
		<description>This double-ended vibrating device is perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couples play. It is made from a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, making it completely waterproof and USB rechargeable to guarantee a fully satisfying experience in any environment. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your possibilities for pleasure. This double-ended design offers you: 8 PLEASURE PATTERNS + 2 EXCLUSIVE APP MODES + 16 INTENSITIES: From a gentle intensity to an overwhelming power. TWO SIDES FOR MUTUAL PLEASURE: Brings double pleasure to couples' play with two vibrating motors on each side. TWISTED SENSORY RIDGES: Crafted with soft sensory edges to transmit sensations to more nerve endings. FEATURES: Modes: 8 pleasure patterns + 2 exclusive App modes Intensities: 16 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for couples or solo play Size: Double-ended LELO has established itself as the luxury pleasure brand, leading the market in design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is not just a pleasure toy brand; it is a self-care movement aimed at those who know that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of ecstasy without shame, the pleasure of discovering all the wonders of one's own body, empowering our customers with the confidence that allows them a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-boomerang-double-ended-vibrator-purple?variant=53702790512977</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-boomerang-double-ended-vibrator-luvmechanics-7737229.jpg?v=1778150724</mainImage>
		<price>189.25</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245680</productCode>
		<quantity>8</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260315</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702790545745</ID>
		<name>BOOMERANG DOUBLE ENDED VIBRATOR-Purple</name>
		<description>This double-ended vibrating device is perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couples play. It is made from a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, making it completely waterproof and USB rechargeable to guarantee a fully satisfying experience in any environment. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your possibilities for pleasure. This double-ended design offers you: 8 PLEASURE PATTERNS + 2 EXCLUSIVE APP MODES + 16 INTENSITIES: From a gentle intensity to an overwhelming power. TWO SIDES FOR MUTUAL PLEASURE: Brings double pleasure to couples' play with two vibrating motors on each side. TWISTED SENSORY RIDGES: Crafted with soft sensory edges to transmit sensations to more nerve endings. FEATURES: Modes: 8 pleasure patterns + 2 exclusive App modes Intensities: 16 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for couples or solo play Size: Double-ended LELO has established itself as the luxury pleasure brand, leading the market in design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is not just a pleasure toy brand; it is a self-care movement aimed at those who know that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of ecstasy without shame, the pleasure of discovering all the wonders of one's own body, empowering our customers with the confidence that allows them a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-boomerang-double-ended-vibrator-purple?variant=53702790545745</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-boomerang-double-ended-vibrator-luvmechanics-9164093.jpg?v=1778150722</mainImage>
		<price>189.25</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245682</productCode>
		<quantity>18</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260292</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<ID>53702790578513</ID>
		<name>BOOMERANG DOUBLE ENDED VIBRATOR-Red</name>
		<description>This double-ended vibrating device is perfect for intense pleasure during solo or couples play. It is made from a single piece of silicone that keeps it airtight, making it completely waterproof and USB rechargeable to guarantee a fully satisfying experience in any environment. For an even better experience, activate the LELO™ app and you can access two exclusive modes designed to expand your possibilities for pleasure. This double-ended design offers you: 8 PLEASURE PATTERNS + 2 EXCLUSIVE APP MODES + 16 INTENSITIES: From a gentle intensity to an overwhelming power. TWO SIDES FOR MUTUAL PLEASURE: Brings double pleasure to couples' play with two vibrating motors on each side. TWISTED SENSORY RIDGES: Crafted with soft sensory edges to transmit sensations to more nerve endings. FEATURES: Modes: 8 pleasure patterns + 2 exclusive App modes Intensities: 16 levels Resistance: 100% waterproof and airtight Charging: USB rechargeable Material: Single piece of silicone Use: Perfect for couples or solo play Size: Double-ended LELO has established itself as the luxury pleasure brand, leading the market in design, innovation, technology, and reputation. But LELO is not just a pleasure toy brand; it is a self-care movement aimed at those who know that satisfaction transcends gender, orientation, race, and age. We offer the experience of ecstasy without shame, the pleasure of discovering all the wonders of one's own body, empowering our customers with the confidence that allows them a fulfilling intimate life.</description>
		<link>https://www.luvmechanics.com/products/lelo-boomerang-double-ended-vibrator-purple?variant=53702790578513</link>
		<mainImage>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0938/7478/2545/files/lelo-boomerang-double-ended-vibrator-luvmechanics-8841629.jpg?v=1778150723</mainImage>
		<price>189.25</price>
		<brand>LELO</brand>
		<productCode>D-245681</productCode>
		<quantity>16</quantity>
		<fileUnder>Erotska pomagala</fileUnder>
		<curCode>EUR</curCode>
		<stock>in stock</stock>
		<deliveryCost>6.90</deliveryCost>
		<EAN>7350167260308</EAN>
		<deliveryTimeMin>4</deliveryTimeMin>
		<deliveryTimeMax>8</deliveryTimeMax>
	</Item>
</CNJExport>